¬ Generated by BinEditor v3.0
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_AZTECS_DESCR}The Chaos Dwarf Empire is sited amidst the Mountains of Mourn and the adjoining eastern part of the Dark Lands. It is a stark and cheerless place, where nature has rent the ground and burst the mountains apart. Amongst the peaks volcanoes spew black smoke into the filthy sky. In the plains the stench of tar pits and oil pools hangs heavily in the air. Steaming lava from beneath the earth's crust covers the ash wastes with a blanket of bubbling magma.\n\nAlmost nothing can grow in the Dark Lands. The dim light and choking air combine to ensure that the land remains devoid of vegetation except for a few straggly black thorns. The volcanoes and gaping pits bring up all kinds of minerals and gems from beneath the earth: gold and silver, iron and cooper, diamons and sapphires, as well as sulphur, oil and tar. It is a land rich in the materials that Dwarfs especially covet.\n\nThe huge and monstrous Tower of Zharr-Naggrund, the City of Fire and Desolation stands on the plain of Zharrduk. This monstrous city is fashioned from black obsidian and stained with the red glow of a thousand diabolic furnaces. Where Dwarfs shun magic the Chaos Dwarfs embraced it and became mighty sorcerers, the creators of arcane machineries and horrific engines. They built the Tower of Zharr-Naggrund in the shape of a mountain rising tier upon tier to its summit. At its top they built a temple to their evil god Hashut, the Father of Darkness.\n\nThe refuse of thousands of years of labour fills the Plain of Zharrduk where industry tears at the earth, pock-marking the surface with ugly scars of endavour. Beneath the flickering flames of countless forges untold thousands of slvaes, creatures of many races captured in war or traded from the Orcs of the west, work at the enterprises of the Chaos Dwarfs.
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_AZTECS_TITLE}Chaos Dwarfs Expedition
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_BYZANTIUM_DESCR}Shaped like an arm wrapped around the shoulders of the Middle Mountains, almost the whole of the province of Ostland is covered by the ominous Forest of Shadows. Long ago, during the expansions of the first millenium, the Counts of Ostland pushed their boundaries deep into what would become Kislev, founding colonies to hold what they had taken. These efforts eventually failed, with Ostland forced to renounce her last claims to Kislevite territory at the time of the Ungol invasions, thanks to the treachery of the Talabheim Emperors. Now the only territory of Ostland not covered in forest is the wind-swept Northern March from Salkalten to the Kislev border. Ostland is a land ravaged by war, with many areas warped by Chaos. Some openly doubt whether she can recover. The Forest of Shadows, which runs southwest from the Nordland border to the river Talabec, is what most people think of when they think of Ostland. Dark, dreary, and overgrown, the Forest of Shadows is like a mad wizard's attic; many bizarre secrets lie within it, some older than the Empire and best left undiscovered. It does not give up its secrets easily, and many residents of Ostland are sure the forest resents their presence, and that even after thousands of years, it has never adjusted to having Humans and their axes and fires under its eaves. Woodsmen and others who venture deep into the forest are sure that, sometimes, when they are not looking, the forest redraws the paths through it to confuse those who anger it, and perhaps even cause their deaths. Hiding within the forest are creatures of Chaos who were there long before current times. Tribes of Beastmen and Giant Spider-riding Goblins compete for food and spoils with outlaws fleeing the Count's justice. The greatest threat comes from bands ruled by the terrible Minotaur Ragush Bloody-Horns, who struck fear into the heart of all who lived in the area between Smallhof and Boven. Known for his insatiable tastes for flesh, Ragush once hung the corpses of the entire population  of a village from the nearby trees for later snacking, calling it his "larder." His whereabout are unknown at this time. The Midle Mountains dominate the southwest of Ostland. Claimed by all the lands surrounding them, Ostland, Hochland, Middenland, and even Nordland, the Middle Mountains are dominated by none. It was once home to a kingdom of Dwarfs who broke away from the Dwarf Empire, Karaz Ankor, during the war against the Elves. Soon after the Greenskins and Skaven fell on the Dwarf Empire and ravaged it, however, the Dwarfs of "Karaz Ghumbul" abandoned their hold and fled the Middle Mountains to return to Karaz Ankor. They sealed the doors, buried them under rock, and destroyed the roads that led to it. To this day, the Dwarfs will not say what drove their people from Karaz Ghumzul, but, as they left the mountains near where Castle Lenkster now stands, the Dwarf priests pronounced a curse on the mountains and everything within them. Since then, many prospectors and adventurers have searched forthe lost Dwarf mines, but none have succeeded, unless they are among those who have never returned.\n\nOstlanders have a reputation for being bull-headed, and, among their Imperial breathren, it is an open question as to which would win in a contest of wills betwee a Dwarf and an Ostlander who has made up his mind on a matter. Descended from the ancient tribe of the Udoses, the Ostlanders have been known for mulishness since the earliest days of the Empire. When Sigmar called the tribes to arms at the Great Moot before the Battle of Black Fire Pass, it is said that it took him three days of argument to convince Wolfila, the Udosian chief, to join. And, when it became clear to everyone else early in the Second Millennium that the Kislevite territories could not be held, the Counts of Ostland insisted on spending blood and treasure to hold on, no matter how much it weakened them. Notoriously thrifty, Ostlanders are known for their ability to survive. Said to be capable of eating anything, there are several mocking songs about the famous 'Stone soup of Ostland.' They are so creative in their frugality that a common joke in the Empire claims that Ostlanders make 'stone soup' with only one stone, for fear of wasting good rocks. While an exaggeration, it is true that Ostlanders are skilled in getting the most use out of what they have to work with and for being loath to throw anything away that might still be useful. This conservatism has at times cost them, as when von Raukov's precedessors refused to adopt gunpowder weapons, because that would mean wasting perfectly good swords and spears. Ostlanders, like most Imperials, honour all the gods and celebrate their feast days. If one god is favoured over another, however it is Sigmar, who is worshipped with a degree of devotion not often seen in the east of the Empire. Surrounded by lands that lean towards Ulric and Taal and Rhya, few know why this is so, though many offer explanations. Devout Ostlanders say it seems from the time when, soon after the founding of the Empire, a great dragon ravaged Ostland. The other electors and their armies were afraid to face the beast, so Sigmar came alone and killed it after a great fight alongside the Ostland Count. Even the smallest Ostlander village sports multiple shrines to Sigmar.\n\nDeep within the heart of the Forest of Shadows, somewhere in the triangle between Smallhof, Ferlangen, and Bohsenfels, there is a small clearing with a grim, horrifying history. At its centre is a single weather-worn standing stone twice the height of a man. It is so stained and discoloured that few can guess what the stone's original hue was. Now, tainted with untold aeons of blood sacrifices, a rich rusty tone colours the whole stone, indeed seeming to arise from within it. The stone itself has four sets of ancient iron manacles hammered into it, each rusted with time and flecked with dried gore. The grass around the stone is littered with bones: Human, Elf, Dwarf, Hafling-even Beastmen and Orc. The once-shining armour of bold knights lies rusting alongside the obscene garb of Chaos warriors. To the north of the stone, with all sockets facing north toward the Chaos Waste, sits a vast pile of skulls, both old and fresh, each of which is silent acknowledgement that this place is sacred to Khorne, the Blood God and Skull Lord. The current "keeper" of this shrine is Bogoslav Tammas, a warrior of Khorne. He seeks victims among the inhabitants of eastern Ostland, Human or otherwise. Those he does not kill immediately he brings back to the fane for torture and sacrifice.\n\nNestled among the foothills of the Middel Mountains, Wolfenburg is the capital of Ostland and a beautiful city which is the crossroad of trade moving overland between Kislev and the Empire. Its great walls give protection from the things lurking in the Forest of Shadows, and the von Raukovs had brought order and stability to the land after the inept rule of the von Tassenincks.
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_BYZANTIUM_TITLE}The Grand Principality of Ostland
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_DENMARK_DESCR}NEVER 
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_DENMARK_TITLE}Chaos
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_ENGLAND_DESCR}Long have the Asur, or more commonly known as High elves, stood as a beacon of light challenging the forces of Chaos wherever it may be found. As they are amongst the oldest races in the world, the knowledge and skills that they have acquired over the years will be essential in the conflict that is to come. The Asur magicians are amongst the most powerful in the world, as they have had centuries to refine their abilities and they do not hesitate to use their powers against any servant of Chaos. And even though that the High elves may still be suffering from the loss of the great Sundering and from fighting against their dark brothers for so long, the resoulution of the Asur has never faltered.\n\nAnd now as their eternal enemy yet again musters in the north, the Asur draws out to meet them on the battlefield once more.. Rest assured, wherever the enemy may go, the High elves will be there in the forefront of the fight, striking down upon them with swift justice and retribution. The Asur will never stop their campaign against the darkness that resides in the north, they will stand triumphant or they will fall.\n\nThe armies of the High elves may lack in numbers, but the skills and bravery of the elvish warriors can still outmatch any enemy that they may come across. Their skills with the blade as well as the bow, is amongst the finest there is to find and is by far enough to conquer any foe.
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_ENGLAND_TITLE}High Elves Expedition
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_FRANCE_DESCR}Ostermark is in the fat east of the Empire, where the Emperor's writ stops at the bounderies of wild Kislev and the kingdoms of the Dwarfs in the World's Edge Mountains. It is a sombre, bleak land of vast moors between two arms of the Great Forest. Snowfalls blanket the land in winter, while the spring thaw turns most of its roads into muddy quagmires. Even is Summer, the sunlight seems to have a weakened, tentative quality to it, as if it is not sure it belongs there. Ostermark is divided into four main regions. In the north, there is the arm of the Great Forest known locally as the "Gryphon's Wood" that follows the line of the Upper Talabec and contains the capital, Bechafen. In the south, along the banks of the Stir, the expanse of the Great Forest near Essen, when spoken of at all, is referred to as the Dead Wood, for the dead city of Mordheim lies in its midst. Between these two arms but south of the Brunwasser river are the central moorlands, a vast expanse of low hills, fen lands, and shallow lakes that is sparsely inhabited, save for the heards of sheep and some scattered villages. North of the Brunwasser between the World's Edge Mountains and the end of Gryphon's Wood are large tracts of rolling grasslands. Well-suited to raising horses, these lands have often been fought over by Ostermarkers and their Kislevite neighbours. The Gryphon's Wood around Bechafen has long been the centre of Ostermark's political and economic life, especially since the destruction of the old capital at Mordheim in 1999 IC. The region's main exports are lumber and riverboats, the latter often built on the spot from some of the trees harvested that season. Ostermarkers largely avoid the Dead Wood in the south. Traffic between Krugenheim in Talabecland and Essen or Karak Kadrin in the montains beyond either travels along the Stir or takes a roundabout route through the Bleak Moors. The woods have had a frightening reputation ever since Mordheim's destruction. None live there, and few willingly enter it. Locals swear that they can hear screams coming from the wood at night, and that any who enter it will come back mad and mutated-if they come back at all. Some blame the anger of the gods, others the weird powers of the stone that fell from the sky that legendary night, but, whatever the reason, nothing natural lives within these woods now. Sometimes a thing escapes from the woods and goes on a rampage amongst the farms and villages, until at last the frightened people hunt it down and kill it, burning the body on the spot.\n\nOstermark has long been an avenue for conquest, whether by invaders attacking the Empire or Imperial armies on the march to Kislev. Originally settled by a minor tribe named the Ostagoths, Orcs, Goblins, and Trolls frequently raided Ostermark in the days before Sigmar founded the Empire. Stout defenders of their homes and fortified villages, the Ostagoths learned to value cooperation between the clans, realising that they were stronger together than apart. This made them open to Sigmar's call for unity, and the Osgaroths contributed a mighty force of axe-men to the army that fought at Black Fire Pass. The battle over, their leader Adelhard accepted the title of Elector Count with a laugh, remarking to Sigmar that theirs was a victory "forseen in the stars." This banter is still recalled in the heraldry of the province-the Star and the crowned "Griffon Victorious." Adelhard and his men took wives and mistresses from among the people of Averland, Stirland, and Talabecland upon their march home. These women were the first of many new blodlines to come into the region, now named Ostermark, or the "Eastern March," for its presence on the frontier. To this mixture were added Ungol elements during the invasions of the mid 18th century, bringing a horse-raising culture to Ostermark's Veldt region. Kislevites would cross the border, too, though more as settlers than conquerors, fleeing the cruelties of the Tsar or natural disasters such as famine or drought. All these elements blended to form a people who, while still recognisably Imperial in culture and language, showed distinct differences from their more western cousins. The people of the League honour all the gods, but Hold Ulric, Morr, Sigmar, and Taal and Rhya in the highest regard. The stone circles of the Old Faith were long ago taken over by Taal's priests, and Bechafen is the site of the largest Sigmarite temle in the east. Ostermarkers have good relations with the Dwarfs of Karak Kadrin, both because of their shared regard for Sigmar and the mutual threat they face from Sylvania, and  most recently, the increase of Chaos activities.\n\nSituated on the south bank of the Uper Talabec, Bechafen is a compact city crowded behind its defensive walls. Buildings are narrow and tall, and lean at dizzying angles over alleys that are more like darkened tunnels. Built from the dark wood of the Great Forest, Bechafen's structures have a gloomy look that no amount of whitewash and coloured trim can dispel. Bechafen is the capital of Ostermark, and has been since the destruction of Mordheim in 2000 IC. The Princes of Bechafen, the Hertwig family, have traditionally held the Chancellor's post since then, in recognition of their service in the aftermath of the disaster. Though the position is hereditary, it must be confimed by unanimous vote of the other Council members. By decree of the Emperor, the Chancellor is also named Elector Count of Ostermark. Bechafen is famous for its boatyards, where some of the finest river craft in the Empire are made. There are also two water-powered sawmills here, a gift of the King of Karak-Kadrin. These turn the logs brought down-river into more easily transported planks. Unfortunately, they are also favourite places for Bechafen's criminal gangs to dispose of people who have crossed them.
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_FRANCE_TITLE}The League of Ostermark
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_HRE_DESCR}Westernmost of the Empire's Great Provinces, the Reikland is the seat of the Imperial Government and the richest, most cosmopolitan province in the Empire-and not just because Reiklanders say so. From north to south, from the edge of the Wastlenad to the borders of Wissenland, Reikland is blessed with fertile farmland, vineyards, and dairy fields that produce a surplus of products for export. The mines of the Grey Mountains yield many valuable ores and stones, from iron and gold to marble and gems, whilst the Reikwald Forest, generally safer than woods in other parts of the Empire, yields valuable timber that supports a thriving boat-building industry. Government patronage helps, too. The Emperors, who since Wilhelm overthrew Dieter in the 25th century have also been the Elector Counts of the Reikland, have lavished Imperial largesse on their home province. Canals, road-building, programs to improve the methods of farming, encouragement of the development of free towns and the mercantile classes-all these have served to make the Reikland a gem among the Empire's provinces. Although most of the Reikland's trade travels by water, a significant amont goes by land over the two main passes across the Grey Mountains to Bretonnia, Axe-Bite Pass and the Grey Lady Pass. The passes are guarded by Imperial fortresses at Helmgart and Ubersreik, both to defend against Human and non-Human raiders living in the mountains, and to keep an eye on the Bretonnians, with whom relations have not always been friendly. The snows of winter close both passes regularly, and travellers are advised to cross them only well after the spring thaws.\n\nReiklanders are generally descended from Sigmar's Unberogen tribe, which took the lead in founding the Empire. As a consequence, the modern Reiklanders consider themselves the natural leaders of the Empire and feel that the other provinces should defer to them. To their kinsmen in other parts of the Empire, Reiklanders instead appear as know-it-alls and busybodies who cannot stop themselves from butting into other people's business. Reiklanders have adopted Sigmar's message of Imperial unity wholeheartedly. They take a keen interest in the affairs of the other Provinces, and often point out that "something should be done" when terrible fates befall their neighbours. Robust supporters of the military, many young Reikland nobles enter the army to make their names and fortune. Considered natural "officer material," the chances of advancement are considerably better for those of Reikland birth, much to other's disgust. Reiklanders almost always answer an Imperial call-ta-arms in large numbers, and feel as if it is their duty to come to the aid of less-fortunate parts of the Empire. Merchant Guilds want to see the Emperor strengthened against the Electors, and therefore call for unitary trade laws overseen by Imperial officials, something the Electors fiercely resist. Although they honour all the gods, Reiklanders generally see Sigmar as their special patron, for he was once one of them. Other popular deities are Dyrath, a regional name for Rhya whom the Reiklanders of Vorbergland honour as the patroness of fertility, and Shallya, whose temples and hospices are frequent recipients of gifts and bequests from wealthy Reiklanders. Although tolerated and formally respected, the cult of Ulric is not popular in the Reikland because of the age-old rivalry between his cult and Sigmar's.\n\nCapital of the Empire, Altdorf is by far its largest city. Home to the Emperor in his twin roles as ruler of the Empire and Elector Count of the Reikland, Altdorf is one of the most important cities in the Old World. Diplomats come from all the known lands to conduct negotiations here, whilst nobles and wealthy commoners send their children here to be educated and find a suitable spouse. Along with the famed Altdorf University, the capital is also home to the Orders of Magic, which teach the various specialities of Imperial Wizardry. Situated at the confluence of the Reik and Talabec rivers, Altdorf is one of the commercial centres of the Empire, and its counting houses and merchants have grown wealthy because of all the trade that must pass through their port. Altdorf has its darker side, too, behind the glitter of the Imperial Palace and the majestry of the Cathedral of Sigmar. Grinding poverty exists along the waterfront and other areas, where workers and beggars scratch out a bare living as their work makes fat merchants and corrupt government officials wealthy. Many trapped here and in other poor areas seek release in drugs and alcohol. In the fortress palace of the witch hunters, suspected worshippers of Chaos and their victims alike are tortured for what they can reveal; too often, the black nets of the Order catch the innocent, too. For the new arrival, Altdorf is a city of opportunity and danger.
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_HRE_TITLE}The Grand Principality of Reikland
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_HUNGARY_DESCR}Never has a land been so forsaken by nature and light as Sylvania. Very close to uninhabitable, Sylvania's dark and deep forests full of despair and hunger make every living soul shiver in fear. Moorlands and swamps of dead where only motion lies within unholy winds of magic.\n\nZombies and skeletons lie underneath nearly every inch of soil, thus ensuring that no life, no one will ever forget who rules these lands. Once in few decades the mighty vampire lords arise for glorious slaughter, and when defeated they wait and wait until human memory of them is nothing more than frightening stories for children. Then, they come again with thirst stronger than anything, with will of steel and without any fear. And the storms of magic dance with black and forbidden words of necromancers, Brother in arms die to raise as unspeakble horrors who kill, feast and maim until everything that is alive will belong to their endless army. Throne of Immortal Emperor- that is the only dream of vampire Counts of Sylvania ever since Vlad von Carstein marched with his hordes of undead for the first time.\n\nAfter unfortunate defeat of Mannfred von Carstein at Hel Fenn we have survived, we have rebuilt, and now your reward is before you My lord, the Throne of Endless Tears is within your grasp. To war!
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_HUNGARY_TITLE}Sylvania
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_KALMAR_UNION_DESCR}The highlands where the Grey Mountains and Worlds Edge Mountains meet are known as the Vaults, and are inhabited by fierce mountain clans who guard the few passes and exort a heavy toll from merchants travelling between the Empire and the lands to the south. These mountain people sometimes travel down into the Reikland to join the Empire's armies. East of here is a large, wild area called the Border Land or the land of the Border Princess. This realm is extremely dangerous, full of marauding Orcs and wolf-riding Goblins as well as the worst kind of Men - bandits, brigands and outcasts from the rest of the Old World. These are new lands that adventurers and brave settlers are trying to civilise, and eventually where they will raise new cities and found new realms. Meanwhile it is a dangerous, but potentially profitable, place where honest Men live behind high wooden stockades under the protection of dispossessed nobles called Border Princes.
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_KALMAR_UNION_TITLE}Border Princes
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_LITHUANIA_DESCR}Tzeentch is the god of change, of magic and of deceit. Tzeentch knows the fate of every being in the universe and he manipulates mortals and gods alike in his convoluted schemes- Not to achieve an specific goal, no, constant change is Tzeentch`s only motivation.\n\nHis Worshippers might not be as numerous as those of Khorne and they might not be as tough as the followers of Nurgle; Yet one shoulnd`t underestimate the might of his legions. For the chosen ones of Tzeentch aren`t just skilled warrios, but also great sorcerers and cunning schemers. Among his legions are also the most hideous abominations, for he is also the god of mutation and he likes to "bless" his followers, who gladly embrace the change.\n\nWhen the legions of Tzeentch go to war, reality is usually the first casualty. The Sky over an army of Tzeentch is charged with raw, magical energy and reality itself is altered to suit the needs of his generals. \n\nStrong walls might crumble to dust; The enemy general might become insane; The stocks of an besieged city might rot within hours; Arrows fired at the followers of Tzeentch might turn to ash in midair; Long awaited reinforcements might change the sides and an secure castle might turn into an death-trap.\n\nThe Lord of Change enjoys such twists of fate, and tell me, when reality bows to his will, who might oppose him?
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_LITHUANIA_TITLE}Tzeentch Followers
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_MILAN_DESCR}Comprising the eastern and of the Drakwald Forest, Hochland is a heavily wooden province bounded by the Middle Mountains in the northeast, and the rivers Drakwasser, Talabec, and Wolf's Run on the west, south, and east, respectively. West beyond a strip of Hochland on the left bank of the Drakwasser lies Middenland, and Talabecland is to the south, while Ostland girds Hochland's east and north. Deep within Hochland are the Weiss Hills, a treacherous mixture of hill contry and fens watched over by lonely Fort Schippel. Though mostly covered in forest, the farms along the river banks and around the villages are fertile thanks to the many rivers and streams that flow south from the uplands of the Middle Mountains. This makes Hochland self-sufficient in food, although luxury victuals have to be imported from Middenheim and Talabheim. Heavy snows in the winted and rains in the spring make Hochland towns susceptible to flooding, though the prior ruling house of Tussen-Hochen invested heavily in dikes to control the floodwaters. nHochland's main trade is in timebr and woodcrafts. Thick woods of oak and sycamore grow in the south, while pine and cedar are in the north. Guilds of lumbermen cut down the trees, trim the trunks, and float the logs down-river to mills in Esk, Bergendorf, Krudenwald, and Hergig. The logs are then bought by brokers, loaded on barges, and shipped out.\n\nHochanders are for the most part descended from the proud Cherusen tribe. Having mingled for some time within the Taleutens of Talabecland, the tribe eventually left the lands of the Great Forest and migrated to a small area near the Middle Mountains. Amidst verdant woods filled with game, these people had found the home they wanted. Less warlike than their neighbours, they contented themselves with hunting, fishing, and singign praises to Taal and Rhya. When other tribes or war bands of Orcs or Beastmen would raid, the early Hochlanders would melt back into their forests, using craft to defeat their enemies. By the time of Sigmar, the Hochlanders, had become skilled scouts and skirmishers, and made valuable contributions to Sigmar's wars. In return, he made their Chief Aloysus a Count of the Empire, much to the annoyance of the Talabeclander Count, who felt the tries of kinship gave him the right to rule Hochland.\n\nThe capital of Hochland, Hergig is home to the Ludenhof family and was once the site of a mighty fortress. It was also home to the Hochland College of Sorcery, a school licensed by the Emperor for the academic study of magic and its theory. With quarries nearby, the town before the was was rebuilding itself as a modern place of stone and bricj, its small Dwarf Quarter supplying their skills in the construction. It is also the site of the Gate of the East bridge, which in the past has been the focus of battles between the expansionist Counts of Ostland an Hochlanders.
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_MILAN_TITLE}The Grand Barony of Hochland
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_MONGOLS_DESCR}The Dark Elves, or Druchii as they call themselves, were once inhabitants of the legendary island of Ulthuan. They regard themselves as the only true heirs to the first and mightiest Phoenix King, Aenarion the Defender. The invading hosts of Chaos had been defeated but had left Aenarion dead and the Elves of Nagarythe saw it only natural that his son Malekith should rise to the throne. However, the council refused and this ultimately exploded into a civil war, known as the Sundering. Ulthuan itself was torn apart as the two forces clashed all across the isle, though ultimately Naggarythe sunk beneath the waves and the remaining Druchii fled to Land of Chill.Today the Druchii have mastered their new desolate homeland and sail the seas, exploring, raiding and on occasion invading Ulthuan, seeking to reclaim their old home. Their hatred is unmatched, their skill formidable and finally their resolve unshakable. The mighty Witch King Malekith reigns supreme still and the armies of the Druchii march at his bidding into the world to spread the terror of the Dark Elves.
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_MONGOLS_TITLE}Dark Elves
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_MOORS_DESCR}Pieces from Goblins: A vermin Incarnate by brother Lorentz the Pious:\n\nImperial year 2257The first incursion into goblin territory yielded no substantial results. Field commander Erik von Hertz led our troops into a glorious victory, chasing the goblin filth into the same holes they originated from but I´m yet to wonder whatever these cowardly creatures contain a sentient life or follow a crude animal instinct. They seem capable of producing their own weapons and armor, but they could just as likely be stolen from ambush victims or looted from nearby garrisons. Still, they seem capable of herding, we lost Captain Furmarch's whole company when the goblins released their squigs. They threw themselves at the soldiers, chewing of armour pieces and even swallowing soldiers heads whole. At the end of the "battle", a shaman appeared to rally his cowardice underlings, sprouting fireballs from his fingers and lashing the goblins into a frenzy. The tap was already shut though and Eriks handgunners launched a massive volley to end the goblin filth. \n\nThis particular tribe of goblins seem to worship the moon, displaying banners and paintings of a faced crescent moon. They are also shy of sunlight and only move above surface during the night, dressing in black garments to hide their skin from the righteous beams of light. Perhaps that's a fitting appendex for them, Night goblins? They also showcase a higher ferocity levels than other tribes. Seeking to take fight sometime instead of running away as most of their "kinsmen". More research into this is needed. \n\nFor the glory of the Empire and the eternal grace of Sigmar!"
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_MOORS_TITLE}Night Goblins
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_NORWAY_DESCR}Khorne, the Blood God, is said to be the mightiest of all the Chaos Gods, for he is rage incarnate. Known by many names, every action taken where blood is spilled is in his name, whether it's intended or not. The sheer primal ferocity of Khorne is apparent in his followers. Many see them as degenerate blood maddened warriors, who seek only the shedding of blood regardless of whether it's friend or foes, yet they couldn't be further from the truth. \n\nWhile the tribesmen of the northern nomad's, like the Hung and the Kurgan may occasionally fall to the throws of bloodlust and the berserkergang, the true power of Khorne lies in the Warriors of Chaos, and his Chosen. \n\nAble to fight with the skill and intelligence of a true blademaster, yet also have the strength and speed of a madman see's them overcome foes who outnumber them many times over - the protection afforded by their Chaos Armour is enough to let them let through blows which could kill a normal man, and not need to waste time blocking - all so that the chosen can continue to spill blood.\n\nThe Warriors of the Blood God always follow a simple code - the blood must flow. \n\nIt matters not from whence it flows; all that matters is that it does.
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_NORWAY_TITLE}Khorne Followers
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_NOVGOROD_DESCR}Nurgle is the Great Lord of Decay and the Master of Plague and Pestilence, his carcase is riddled with disease and infestation. Nurgle is also Lord of All because all things, no mater how solid and permanent they seem, are liable to physical corruption. Indeed, the very processes of construction and creation foreshadow destruction and decay. The palace of today is tommorrows' ruin, the maiden of the morning is the crone of the night, and the hope of a moment is but the foundation stone of everlasting regret.\n\nNurgle is probably the greatest showman of all the Chaos Powers and revels in the specticle and drama of battle more than any of the others. The army can perhaps be visualised as a grotesque and macabre carnival. Wild jollity, laughter and mad-cap capering is combined with the most horrible manifestations of disease and deformity, like an insane circus parade of all the worst ills imaginable.\n\nThe warbands flocked to the sound of the drum. The plaguebearers carefully recorded the name of each Champion, announcing his titles as loudly as they were able among the rising laughter and squeaking chatter. The show pleased father Nurgle immensley, he sighed with satisfaction and patted the little Nurgling that had crawled into the crook of his arm and puddled there. With a loving smile the great Daemon plucked the Nurgling from the folds of his arm, caressed it for a moment before popping it whole into its gapping maw.\n\n"Ahh... Gentlecreatures, Children , pretties ... lend your ears to your loving Father, cease thy aimless chatter, banish thy banal burblings....."\n\n"Gentlecreatues our pretties... now is time to sing the songs of fate, for the moment has come for the Dance of Death!" 
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_NOVGOROD_TITLE}Nurgle Followers
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_POLAND_DESCR}The Dwarfs are one of the most ancient races of the Warhammer world. From the beginning of time, their traditional homeland has been the Worlds Edge Mountains, the vast, forbidding mountain chain, that marks the eastern boundary of the Old World. Here in ages past, the Dwarfs built their massive underground strongholds among the high peaks and tumbling chasms. At its height, their real spread from the far north to the distant south, while their mines stretched far beneath the earth itself. These days of glory are now long gone; many strongholds lie in ruins or are occupied by evil creatures, and the great achievements of the past are now nothing more than memories, ancient sagas sung in the half-empty halls of the few surviving Dwarf strongholds.\n\nThe Dwarf strongholds of the World Edge Mountains are remnants of the once great Dwarf empire known by the Dwarfs as Karaz Ankor. This means either the 'Everlasting Realm' or the 'Mountain Realm', the Dwarf word for mountain and extreme durability being the same. The great city of Karaz-a-Karak, called Everpeak in the tongue of Men, lay at the centre of this vast empire. The history of the Everlasting Realm is a long saga of war, treachery and betrayal that has left a bitter legacy in the minds of the Dwarf people.
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_POLAND_TITLE}Karaz Ankor
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_PORTUGAL_DESCR}The Southwestern-most of the Empire's provinces, Wissenland forms a triangle bounded by the Black and Grey Mountains on two sides and the River Reik on the third. Originally confined to the lands west of the Söll River, Wissenland in the 18th century absorbed what was left of Solland after the invasion of the Orc warlord Gorbad Ironclaw. Eight hundred years later, the people of Wissenland still often refer to the land east of the Söll as "old Solland" or "Sudenland," a modern derivation. Like the Reikland, western Wissenland is heavily watered by streams and rivers flowing from the mountains that feed the Söll, which in turn joins the Upper Reik at Pfeildorf. These tributaries are fed by melting snow in the spring, leading to frequent flooding of the towns along their courses. Meissen itself was nearly wiped out in Great Flood of 2484. The farmlands of Wissenland are fertile near the Reik, but as the land rolls towards the mountains it becomes steadily more dry and stony. Chunks of bluish grey flint are so common that many nobles claim the land is good for little but harvesting rocks. Being so close to the mountains, western Wissenland has abandoned all but the barest subsistence farming, instead heavily depending on mining for its wealth. While the Dwarfs of Karak Norn and Karak Hirn claim large areas of the mountains for themselves, negotiations over centuries have secured rights for Humans to mine, too, though this does not stop illegal operations on Dwarf lands. The Dwarfs do not take kindly to what they see as theft, and more importantly, shoddy workmanship.\n\nWissenlanders are descendants of the Merogens, the tribe that settled the area in pre-Imperial days. Like the Unberogen to their north, the Merogens had good relations with the neighbouring Dwarfs, particularly the kingdom of Karak Norn, and they answered in great numbers when Sigmar issued the call to arms before the battle of Black Fire Pass. The influence of Dwarf culture is sais to be the reason so many Wissenlanders are short and practical in their speech. Little time is given for flowery words or fancy phrases, and even less to artists, poets, and foppish Reiklanders. The folk of Wissenland are known to be a dour lot. The fall of Solland was a dark chapter in the Imperial history, and Wissenlanders seem to carry this shame with them. They are a hardy people, given to few words and little emotion. Their stony implacability is known to soften when they are in their cups, and on rare occasions they might break into "The Lament of Solland" or other such lonesome ballad. While all the gods are honoured in Wissenland, Sigmar and Taal and Rhya have special prominence. Sigmar's cult centres in the west, where contract with the Dwarfs is greatest. Both Wissenburg and Meissen have large temples that host shrines for the Dwarf to worship their own deities, whilst upriver from Geschburg in the foothills of the Grey Mountains lies the shrine of Sigmar Protector, a popular pilgrimage spot. It was here in the 14th century that a force of the Elector Count was trapped by marauding Orcs. Their destruction looked certain. According to that legend, at the height of the fighting a great horn was heard, and from nowhere a powerful warrior wielding a hammer appeared to lead the Wissenlanders to victory. Revealing himself as Sigmar, the warrior promised he would always protect their people in their times of need. A monastery has since been built on the spot, and the monks are only too happy to give out pious icons, artefacts, and illuminated prayers in return for "donations."\n\n"The crown that glitters with a thousand jewels," Nuln is the Empire's second city in population, but its first in social life and the arts. It is the home of the Imperial School of Gunnery, which supplies master gunners to the armies of all the Electors. The University of Nuln is an ancient institution, dating back to the earliest days of the Empire. Its scholars are regarded as among the finest in the world, and wealthy parents send their children from as far away as Arabia to study here. Nuln is a city-state, technically free of Wissenland, but still owing allegiance to its Elector Count. This poses little problem for the freewheeling people of the city, for the Elector of Wissenland is also Countess of Nuln. Emmanuelle von Liebwitz, still beautiful in her middle age, loves Nuln and spends almost all her time there, giving grand balls and hosting dinners that last for days. To rid herself of dreary Wissenland, Countess von Liebwitz is negotiating with the Emperor to completely separate Nuln and Wissenland. She would retain Nuln and her electoral vote, whilst the province would be given to the Toppenheimer family, which would also receive an electoral vote. All this would be done in return for large loans to the Emperor's war coffers, a strategy she is coordinating with her colleague in Talabheim.
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_PORTUGAL_TITLE}The Grand County of Wissenland
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_RUSSIA_DESCR}Traveller, look to the North, there we shall stand as the Darkness covers us. For Motherland, for dreams written in ice, for freedom of steppes. Mourn us not, but remember that rose of Winter shall blossom with roar of bear once again.“\n\nFor centuries have our Tzars and Tzarinas enforced the rule of law in these unsteady lands, ever vigilant against new threats. For centuries have we withstood harsh winters and the deadly winds of destruction blowing from the Chaos Wastes. Many great men have been destroyed because of the idleness brought about by peace. The Kislevite soul however never rests, never falters, and when war calls, its voice is heard by the young and the old alike.\n\nOur friendship with the Empire is strong and Kislev renews its oaths to our southern neighbours time and again with the steel of our Winged lancers and the arrows of our marksmen, with the favour being returned frequently over the years. But even the armies of the Empire cannot be everywhere, and though its military might is great it falls on Kislev to be the front line in the battle against Chaos. Night goblins are beginning to stir in the East and at times the drums of an Orc warband sounds through the blades of the long steppe grass.\n\nThe time for war has come again, and may mighy Ursun lead us to victory, else all hope be lost.
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_RUSSIA_TITLE}Kislev
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_SAXONS_DESCR}Bounded by the World's Edge Mountains on the east and on the north, west, and south by the rivers Stir, Aver, and Reik, Stirland is a rugged province of highly mixed terrain. Its reputation as a rural backwater is largely undeserved, for it has many towns of substantial size and it does a brisk trade with the Dwarfs of Zhufbar. Nevertheless, its location away from the centres of power and the presence of the dread lands of Sylvania make people think ill of Stirland. The northern portions along the banks of the Stir are covered with the last reaches of the Great Forest. To the east, beyond Siegfriedhof, the forest thins and breaks up into seperate woods, the feared Hunger and Grim woods, places of foul reputation. Past the Grim Wood, the Grim Wood, the dismal village marks the start of the Hel Fenn, where Imperial forces destroyed the army of Manfred von Carstein, one of the Vampire Counts of Sylvania. The east of Stirland holds the rest of the province in genuine dread, for it is here that one finds benighted Sylvania. From the sombre town of Tempelhof, which has not had a resident priest of Morr in 800 years, to the foothills of the World's Edge Mountains between the Aver Reach and the Stir, Stirland's largest region is a place of fear and gloom. It is said that Ghosts walk freely at night among the Haunted Hills, and the deep fogs of the Sylvanian woods are said to sometimes trap a soul within them, forced to wander forever. The eastern portion of the province is the bleakest, where ancient black castles sit on their craggy peaks like black vultures staring down on the towns below. Sylvania is a place most Stirlanders try to forget about, and the Elector Count's tax collectors come calling only when accompanied by a large armed guard. Even the Dwarfs of Zhufbar avoid Sylvania, preferring the road south to Schramleben and then through the Moot if they wish to travel to Wurtbad.\n\nDescended from the Asoborn tribe of old, Stirlanders are a short, thickset people, much like their Ostermark neighbours. Dark of hair and suspicious of strangers, their bloodline has remained one of the most undiluted in the Empire. Some folk point out this is because they're inbred peasants, but, as the Stirland Nobility are keen to point out, even the most baseborn soul can trace their line back over many generations. Famed for their superstition, Stirlanders are a cautious lot. Also said to be overly rural and backward, Stirlanders are often mocked by the rest of the Empire for their slow pace of life and speech. For their part, the folk of Stirland are proud of their preservation of ancient customs, and of their "long view" of life. Stirlanders in the central portion of the province are known for their dislike of Halflings, for they still resent the 1500-year-old decision that tore away their best farmlands and gave them to "the Shorties." Although this resentment rarely breaks out in violence, the belief that Halflings are thieves at heart is stronger here than in any other part of the Empire. In Wördern there is a tradition, when celebrating a child's birthday, to make a straw-man the size of a Halfling and stuff it with candies and treats he "stole" from the children. Then it is hung from a branch and the blindfolded children whack at it with sticks until it breaks and "gives them back" their candy. Locals deny that drunks have occasionally instead tied up a real Halfling.\n\nCapital of Stirland, Wurtbad rests at the terminus of the Old Dwarf Road, surrounded by the Great Forest. By far the largest town in Stirland, its whitewashed walls and buildings and its busy docks and markets tell of a prosperous trading town. By decree of the Elector Counts, all the wine produced in western Stirland must be sold through Wurtbad, earning the town the sobriquet of "the wine capital of the Empire." Traders come from all over the Empire and beyond to bid on next year's vintages, and the Vintner's Guild is an important political force. The city is ruled by the Haupt-Anderssen family, in their capacities as Princes of Wurtbad. As they are also the Elector Counts, Wurtbad is a regional centre for government and diplomacy. Innkeeping is a respected art in Wurtbad, with the Golden Eagle Inn being a favourite of visiting dignitaries. The town is also famous for its several hot spring baths, and many of the wealthy come "to take the waters." Because the rich and powerful are often guests, spies and assassins regularly ply their traders here. The Count therefore maintains a vigilant secret police force to prevent embarrassing incidents.
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_SAXONS_TITLE}The Grand County of Stirland
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_SCOTLAND_DESCR}Founded by the ancient Teutogens, perhaps the fiercest tribe in Sigmar's confederacy, the Grand Duchy of Middenheim and Middenland (commonly referred to simply as "Middenland") is the powerhouse of the northern Empire. Through military and economic power, it dominates its neighbours to the east and north, Hochland, Ostland, and Nordland. Its influence rivals Reikland and Talabecland, and its great city of Middenheim considers itself the equal of Nuln or Altdorf. Middenland has provided Emperors in the past and looks to do so in the future. When regional crises threaten the Empire, Middenland is considered (and considers itself) the voice of the North. Middenland comprises a vast swath of territory stretching from the River Reik and the Great Northern Road of the Wasteland in the west and southwest, and Hochland and the Middle Mountains to the east. South beyond the Talabec is Talabecland, Middenland's sometime rival for leadership of the Cult of Ulric. To the north are her ally Nordland and the Laurelorn Forest, home of the mysterious and occasionally hostile Wood Elves. That the Elves are hostile because of Middenland's longlasting claims to the Laurelorn is immaterial, since these claims were inherited from the Drakwald Emperors of long ago. The Drakwald itself is a vast, ancient forest running from the edge of the Wasteland to the far end of Hochland. While Mankind has made seetlements there, some deep within it, the forest holds many secrets, and it does not give them up graciously. Dragons terrorised the ancient tribes and early Empire from there, until an Emperor killed the last of their kind. Still, foolhardy treasure hunters brave the depths of the Drakwald to seek the riches of a lost dragon's lair, or perhaps their eggs, which are said to remain fertile forever and only need great heat to hatch. Deep under the forest eaves also lurk Beastmen, descendants of raiders from long ago, who breed and wait, occasionally attacking the lone farm or small group of travellers, until the time comes for Chaos to claim the north. The nobles and burghers of the province occasionally mount expeditions to root them out, but survivors always flee deeper into the forests, to wait again and re-grow their numbers.\n\nMiddenlanders are descendants of the warlike Teutogen tribe. Fierce and unrelenting in their ways, the quickly carved out a kingdom from the harsh lands of the Howling hills, driving the native Jutone tribe into the fog-shrouded depths of the Wasteland. When Sigmar came to them, he found a tribe with an unbending will, and strong sense of honour. Though other tribes had joined under his banner, the Teutogens refused to submit to the future God. Eventually Sigmar was forced to kill their tribal chieftain, Artur, in single combat to prove his strength and worth to the Teutogen peoples. Like all Northerners, Middenlanders are famed for their stubborn ways. This, their Teutogen blood and their "firebrand" tempers has given them a reputation as uncontrollable traditionalists. They hate changes of all types, and defend what they see as "tradition" at all times. They are the last to admit that they are wrong, and the first to challenge an unworthy leader. Whilst those of southern Middenland are less strident than their Drakwald cousins, even they are considered coarse, arrogant, and controlling by the rest of the Empire. Middenlanders are divided along what were once clannish lines, but have now divided into geographical prejudices. At one time the Drakwald region had a distinct identity from the rest of Middenland, producing a lone of notoriously corrupt Emperors. With the collapse of their dynasty and the devastation of the Great Plague of 1111, the power of the Drakwald was decimated. It ceased to exist as a seperate entity when the Emperor Mandred gave it to Middenheim, creating the province as it stands today. Its people are still known as mean-spirited and grasping but seem to be softening over time.\n\nThe City of the White Wolf, home of the cult of Ulric and the greatest city of the north, Middenheim is the rock on which the wave of Archaon's invasion will crash and disperse. Founded before the Empire was born, the giant mountain on which Middenheim sits, called the Fauschlag or Ulricsberg, towers high above the surrounding Drakwald, like an island rising in a sea of green. Four great causeways lead from the ground to the city's gates, connecting Middenheim with the roads to Marienburg, Kislev, Talabheim, and Altdorf. From its ramparts cannon point in all directions, showing the willingness of the people of the White Wolf to do battle anytime, anywhere. Central to the city is its identity as the home of the chief temple of the Cult of Ulric and its High Priest, the Ar-Ulric. The cult's Great Temple dominates the centre of the city, itself a fortress within a fortress. Its battlements are not just for show, and the Templars of the White Wolf who live in the attached barracks are not just for parades. The eternal flame burns bright within its canctum, and the temple will be the last place to fall should Middenheim's walls fail.
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_SCOTLAND_TITLE}The Grand Duchy of Middenheim and Middenland
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_SICILY_DESCR}In law, the writ of Nordland extends from the Ostland border west to the edge of the Wasteland, and north from the Great North Road to the shores of the Sea of Claws. The Elector Counts of Nordland have accumulated an impresive collection of titles and claims over the millennia, which, if enforced, would make them rulers of most of the north of the Empire. Reality has a way of foiling the most grandiose ambitions, however, and the Counts' rule extends to barely half the lands they claim. Two great forests blanker Nordland, leaving Humans to exist in pockets carved out of the solid woodlands and along the barren shoreline. The eastern quarter includes the edges of the Forest of Shadows, which dominates Ostland. It extends as far as the Erengrad-Middenheim Road, crossing it north of Beeckerhoven and finally ending on the banks of the River Salz. The Forest of Shadows has a dark, dread reputation in Ostland, and that reputation has carried over to the people of Nordland. Predatory Giant Spiders are known to lurk deep in the forest, while Beastmen and worse have been seen in increasing numbers since the war began. Lumbering parties rarely travel far into the woods anymore, unless accompanied by armed soldiers. The increased danger has led to a fall in timber harvests, hurting the local economy and leading to rumblings that the Count Theodoric Gausser is not doing his job.\n\nThe people of Nordland are descendents of the ancient Was Jutone tribe. Close brothers to the Was Jutones of Ostland, the Nordland branch of the tribe eventually became estranged from the more easterly settlements of their peoples. Eventually, the early Nordlanders fell in battle, becoming vassals of the belligerent Teutogens, and frequent victims of Norscan raids. During the chaos that reigned in the aftermach of the Great Plague, much of Nordland's coasts of the river valleys were invaded and colonised by the Norscans, leading to a mingling of the tribal bloodlines. Emperor Mandred Ratslayer, faced with graver threats elsewhere, had little time to answer the pleas of the Nordlanders, much to their horror. As time passed and population mixed, the Nordlanders adopted many of the customs of their Norscan cousins. Courts frequently resort to trial by combat, the contest taking place on a white sheet pagged to the ground. The first person to stain the sheet red with his blood is declared the loser and the guilty party. Older houses often have runes carved into their doors and window frames for luck and spiritual protection, and along the coast the longhouse style is still common. At feasts and gatherings, Norscan bragging contests have evolved into more genteel storytelling events, with each speaker trying to outdo the last. So great is the Nordlander love of stories that they have become famour around the Empire as great storytellers. Popular tales range from historical epics to low comedy, mythology, and horror. Renowned hunters and foresters, the Nordlanders' woodland skills are so strong that even Hochlanders and the folk of the Talabec will grudgingly admit that they are "not to bad." Certainly Nordlanders are close to the land. The province has one of the largest communities of Rhya worship in the north of the Empire, contred around the clannish villages south of Hargendorf. The Worship of the Harvest Mother without her consort Taal, is considered particularly dangerous in some circles of thought.\n\nThe capital of Nordland, Salzenmund rests among hills from which flow the tributaries that join to form the Salz. The Elector Counts built a tall castle at the top of the hill overlooking the growing city, once the meeting place for the western scions of the Was Jutone tribe. So narrow is the approach that the keep, named the Jutone's Nest, needs no surrounding curtain wall; just the great keep sits there, watching over the region. It is said by the locals that the Elector Count can see the whole of his province from the window of his throne room, which faces west so he can keep an eye on the Elves of Laurelorn. Salzenmund itself is a sizable town that is currently suffering from the loss of trade along the Erengrad-Middenheim Road. Many travellers and merchants would stop there for its fairs, where even Elven goods are available. Brokers sell timber from the Laurelorn here, too, which commands a high price because of its exquisite grain, lightness, and durability. And Salzmund is home to the Nordland Silvermith's Guild, which controls the trade in finished goods and ingots made from ore found in the nearby Silver Hills. The smiths of Salzmund are known for their high quality work, which is in demand as far away as Estalia and Arabia.
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_SICILY_TITLE}The Grand Barony of Nordland
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_SPAIN_DESCR}Stretching more than 700 miles from east to west, Talabecland occupies the centre of the Empire, bordering on more Grand Provinces than any other. Consequently, it has become a mojor transit route for trade within the Empire, with traffic flowing up and down the rivers Stir and Talabec, and north-south trade making extensive use of the Old Forest Road from Hermsdorf to Talabheim. Elector Count Helmut Feuerbach rules it with an iron hand. The dominant feature of Talabecland is the Great Forest, which stretches from end to end along the province's long axis. Less forbidding than the Forest of Shadows or the Drakwald, the Great Forest is nonetheless home to its share of dangers and mysteries. Although there are isolated villages scattered throughout the forest, and despite the Talabeclanders' skill as woodsmen, the interior of the Great Forest remains a fearful and mysterious place to many. Deep within it lurk bands of Beastmen and Greenskins, as well as maleficent things that have lived there since the dawn of time. The west in particular, in the region of the Barren Hills, is known for the number of Mutants encountered there. Many of the folk of Talabecland make their living form the woods in one way or another, either as foresters, charcoal burners, or trappers. The woodlands themselves are of the same primordial forest that once covered all of the Empire. Formed of oak, birch, and beech in the south, moving towards darker evergreen pines in the north, the woods are pierced now and again with the occasional clearing or rock outcropping. It is in such places that the villages of the woodsfolk can be found. Talabeclanders fear the eastern Barren Hills, a land they consider cursed. More than 100 years ago, to hear country people tell it, the Chaos moon Morrslieb spat upon the world, its spittle landing on what were then called the Green Hills. Soon, most plants and animals within the area died. Those that did not mutated in horrible ways and had to be destroyed by the Elector Count's forces. Today the Barren Hills are shunned by all save a few, either treasure hunters following rumours of lost gold or magical items, or those who think they are protected from the curse.\n\nMost of the people of Talabecland are descendants of the Taleuten tribe, to whom Sigmar gave rulership over all the lands between the Talabec and the Stir. After years of wandering the Great Forest, the Talabec found the Great Crater, a huge bowl in the earth surrounded by a natural wall. The wall itself was pierced by a tunnel. According to legend Krugar, the chief of the Talabec, decided this was a sign from Taal himself and ordered the building of a great city within the crater. Known first as Taalahim, later to become Talabheim, it is the largest city in the east and is considered impregnable. A thickly forested place, Talabecland has a reputation for barbarism and ignorance amongst the other provinces. The folk of Talabecland ignore this nonsense, holding instead a private pride in their forest craft and practical skills. The role of the father is considered especially important to the folk of the Great Woods. Even town-born men take their sons to the woods of a summer, and teach them how follow a trail, light a fire, and catch a meal. This is considered a matter of practicality, just like a Marienburger learning to swim. A lad without a father to patiently teach him the ways of the wood and the bow is considered unlucky indeed. Talabeclanders are a religious people, revering all the gods of the Empire, but holding special reverence for Taal and Rhya. Indeed, Taal's greatest temple is found in the small woods outside Talabheim in the Great Crater. Ulric is also popular, for although not braggarts, Talabeclanders are known for their warlike ways.\n\nTalabheim is the capital of Talabecland and the seat of the Elector Counts. It has for several centuries been a chartered Free City under the rule of the Feuerbach-Untern family and a powerful parliament of nobles. Hide-bound by tradition, Talabheim is known as a city of laws. There are laws governing all aspects of life and behaviour, many dating back to the city's foundation. The confusing morass of often contradictory and capriciously applied laws drives even natives to distraction, makin the Litigant's Guild very wealthy and influential. Outside the wall lies Talabheim's port, Talagaad. A run-down pest hole inhabited by the poorest of the poor, alcoholism and crme are rampant here.
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_SPAIN_TITLE}The Grand Duchy of Talabecland 
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_TEUTONIC_ORDER_DESCR}Of the four grand deities of Chaos, the Dark Prince, Slaanesh is the youngest and weakest. However, one would be foolish to believe that he wields no power.\n\nSlaanesh is pride, Slaanesh is desire. Slaanesh is decadence, Slaanesh is lust. The mightiest Empire might withstand the rage of Khorne, the schemes of Tzeentch and the diseases of Nurgle, yet it will ultimately fall victim to it's own hauteur and crumble - much to the amusement of the Dark Prince.\n\nHis followers are a breathtaking sight, ranging from unearthly beautiful to outrightly debauched. Many soldiers facing a Champion of Slaanesh found themselves unable to follow their original orders, wishing nothing more than to fullfill his every wish.\n\nHowever, each gift of Chaos comes at a price; Those who gift their souls to the Prince of Lust slowly loose their humanity, growing unable to feel anything but the most extreme pain and pleasure. This is why, in battle, warriors of Slaanesh sometimes appear just as mad as followers of Khorne - with the exception that they don't only aim to spill blood, but to inflict maximal pain while doing so.\n\nThe armies of Slaanesh may not be as tough or well armoured as those of Khorne and Nurgle, not as adept in magic as those of Tzeentch, but they posess a deadly grace and speed none of the other Chaos gods is able to muster.\n\nAnd after all, Slaanesh doesn't need a single warrior to achieve victory, for the true battle against the Dark Prince is fought within the very soul of every living creature...
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_TEUTONIC_ORDER_TITLE}Slaanesh Followers
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_TITLE}Storm of Chaos
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_TURKS_DESCR}WAAAAAGH!!!! 'ere we goe ya dumb sod! I´m big warboss now and I say we smash 'em puny 'umie rock buildings! We iz gonna stick 'em wiv choppas, blast 'em wiv 'em rock lobbas 'an nick all ther gear!!Me Big'uns are strong and hunty and will kill 'em who stann' in me way!! Yu' 'arrer boyz fill 'em wif 'arrers, yu' choppa boyz chopp 'em up real gud', them black orks will smash yer 'eads in if yu go run like little pansy-elfses!! An 'en we bash 'em dwarfs up for good, an pile 'ere bones outside me hutt and make it look real flash'd up!!\n\nAn 'en we got'z 'em big chaos boyz, 'ey got 'em demons 'an that sort of magic nonnwatz. Me pick me teef wif em' demon horns, Gork got'z way moor' power than any of 'em godz!! Me let 'em fink t'ere real smart but me smarter van 'em, I'll let 'em 'ave orkish swords 'an orkish 'axes 'an 'ey won't even notice!!!!"" 
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_TURKS_TITLE}Orcs and Goblins
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_VENICE_DESCR}Lacking the great forests that cover much of the rest of the Empire, Averland is a series of sun-drenched rolling plains running roughly northwest to southeast between the rivers of the Upper Reik, the Aver, and the Blue Reach. To the west lie Wissenland and Nuln, while the plains rise in the east to meet the Black and World's Edge Mountains. Within the mountains are the kingdoms of the Dwarfs, which stand between Averland and the Border Princes.\n\nAverland is a fertile country, its plains watered by the annual floods of the great rivers that border it. In some years the waters crest far higher than usual, flooding many of the cities and towns along their banks. Averlanders see this as a price to pay for having abundan crops. Away from the rivers, the plains rise gently to the geographical centre of the province, where the Old Dwarf Road and Agbeiten road meet at Heideck. The interior of Averland is given over to small villages of tenants that do the vast fiels of the rural nobility. In the west and central portions of the province, nobles devote themselves mostly to the raising of the famous Averland longhorn cattle.\n\nThe people of Averland are a curious lot. Folk whisper the proud bloodline of the Brigundians has curdled somewhat, with time, inbreeding and the looming influence of the Black Mountains. Already considered a little 'moon-touched' by most of the Empire, the accession of Elector Count 'Mad' Marius Leitdorf caused much amusement at Averland's expense. At their best, Averlanders are open, passionate, and honest about just what they're thinking. If a funeral happens to stike them as funny, well, they'll laugh. If someone upsets them, they'll let them know. At their worst Averlanders are contradictory, flighty, and changeable. Astrology and other such superstition is very popular in Averland, and merchants will often ditch a deal made in 'an unfavoutable hour' or on an 'unlucky day'. Marius Leitdorf, known for his dark depressions and strange rages, was considered typical of the Averland temperament. Even troll slayers have been heard to say that Averlanders are 'a bit odd in the head'. Their changeable nature has resulted in many jokes about the regiments of Averlanders retreating in the face of fear, something that irritates them to no end-they resent any implication that their martial prowess is any less than that of any other state.\n\nOne of Averland's significant place if Averheim-site of the main camp of the Brigundians. It has been the chief city of the land between Aver and Reik since before Sigmar was born. It sits on a bluff above the Aver, and so is immune from its occasional high floods. At the highest point of the city, at the end of the road leading from Pfungzig and Heideck, the fortress of the Elector Counts sits behind powerful walls, its towers commanding a view for miles around. A famous monument in the city is the Pillar of Skulls, making the high point of Gorbad Ironclaw's army's efforts in Averland in the 18th century. Although the Averburg itself has never fallen, the city was penetrated and Gorbad's forces made it as far as the Plenzeplatz, the city's main square. There the Grand Count and his personal guard, and the remaining soldiers of Averland set upon them. Slaughteres by the hundreds, Gorbad's army was forced to move on, and the Elector Count ordered a monument built from the skulls of the dead Orcs. To this day, it is said that blood drips from the eye sockets of some of the skulls on the Night of Mystery.
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_VENICE_TITLE}The Grand County of Averland
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_NORMANS_DESCR}The Norsii were an ancient tribe of men that were the ancestors of the Norse, and one of the later human tribes who began to migrate to the fertile Reik Basin and surrounding areas during the age that preceded the coming of Sigmar. Unlike the eastern tribes that would become the antescendants of the Imperial states, the Norsii were an earlier migration to the Reik Basin from the far northern lands beyond the Kislevite Steppes. According to the records of the Northern Dwarfs, primarily the Saga of Dread Yngvarr Iovarsson, the arrival of the Norsii to the fertile lands of the south is dated reliably as having taken place in -1012 IC, 20 years before the later Black-Fire Pass migration of the Imperial tribes. In the saga, Yngvarr is described as having made contact with various exceptionally savage and warlike tribes of primitive humans, who come to span the lands we now known as Kislev, Ostland and Nordland over the course of their migrations. These tribes included the Ungols, Frikings, Roppsmenn and, most terrifying and significant of all, the Chaos-worshiping Norsii.\n\nAccording to the sagas and traditions passed down from the ancient tribes regarding the earliest stages of the Reik Basin's settlement, the most brutal and depraved of the Norsii clans were driven back across the northern seas by the combined efforts of the tribes of the later Blackfire Pass migration in a battle that had seen the rest of the bloodthirsty Northmen confined to the fringes of the land, the frozen wastes beyond the Middle Mountains. These exiled Norsii clans would come to be known as the Lost Tribes, and were believed by the southern tribes to have perished in the cursed lands of the North.\n\nHowever, this was not the case, and it was not long after their exile that the longships of the Lost Tribes began to sail once more from the frozen homeland of the Norse, and it was during the reign of High King Varag Skulltaker that the bonds between the Lost Tribes and their cousins yet residing in the Reik Basin were rekindled and the Norsii were once more a reunited whole. The Norsii were also unique in that, as a result of their northern origins, they did not hold to the gods of the other tribes, such as Ulric and Taal, but rather their own traditional pantheon -- the Chaos Gods, and dedicated themselves particularly to the blasphemous worship of the god Khorne, whom they venerated by his ancient Dark Tongue name of 'Kharneth', or "Lord of Rage." Bloodthirsty and warlike, the Norsii were ever the bane of their southern neighbours. Feared and despised for the devastating brutality and the butchery of their catastrophic invasions. Master sailors of dreaded wolf-headed longships, the Norsii raiders were ever the terror of the northern coastlines.
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_NORMANS_TITLE}Norsca
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_SKAVEN_DESCR}The Skaven, sometimes known as Ratmen, or the Children of the Horned Rat, are a malevolent and diabolical race of large humanoid rat-creatures that inhabits a massive inter-continental underground empire known in thier tongue simply as the Under-Empire, where at the very heart of Skavendom lies the horrific city of Skavenblight, the species capital city and the probable birthplace of the Skaven race. The Skaven as a whole are one of the World's most numerous species, often having a population number of millions in the Old World alone, as these creature breed at an extraordinarily high rate. Such is the numbers of the Skaven race that these scavengers live within the filth and garbage of the intelligent races of the Old World, such as the kingdoms and cities of Mankind, where from below they would endlessly scheme for the inevitable conquest of the surface.\n\nThe main skaven religion that dominates nearly every single aspect of the Under-Empire is the veneration and worship of a minor Chaos God, known by many names, but its well known title is that of the Horned Rat. This deity takes the form and appearance of a massive horned rat, with its symbol of power being the number 13, along with the rough equilateral triangle and the horned bell as its holy icon. For the few people that do know of their existence, eye witnesses describe the Skaven race as an often unjust society, where characteristics such as wit and strength are held foremost above all other traits, whist the ideals of compassion and cooperation are often denied existence within this Under-Empire.\n\nAs such the Skaven as a whole are divided, often far more divided then any other race in the Old World, due to the fact that this society promotes methods such as backstabbing, assassination, and betrayal as both an essential and traditional path to progress through their society. Such ruthless lack of cooperation has led many of their kind to do things that would endanger or perhaps ensure the death of nearly hundreds of their own kind -- all for the greed or ambition of just one Skaven. Such corruption and disunion has caused the Skaven race to splinter into hundreds, if not thousands of highly unstable, clan-based societies, where each Clan has a certain skill or trait that is often seen as "unique" to other Skaven communities, providing either food, goods, or weapons of war for the trade of other goods made by other Skaven clans. It is believed by the Skaven that their race is the supreme race, with their malevolent God promising his children that one day they will inherit the world as their very own. 
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_SKAVEN_TITLE}Skaven
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_TIMURIDS_DESCR}The Tomb Kings were once rulers of Nehekhara , a vast, fertile land of many war-torn kingdoms. The divided land was eventually unified by the First King of Nehekhara, King Settra. King Settra was a beloved ruler that led Nehekhara into a golden age, yet time was not on his side. As Settra grew older he began to turn his gaze towards extending his rule into the afterlife. He charged his priests of the 'Mortuary Cult', who tended the mummified remains of the past rulers, to use their magics to develop a spell for everlasting life. After many years the priests were able to develop two spells: the first was one that would simply prolong life, the user would still age indefinitely, and the other would allow for the resurrection of the user. With promises that they would find a spell for true eternal life, the priests cast the magics that would allow them to reanimate the dead onto King Settra as he died. It would be this spell that would cause the eventual damnation of all of Nehekhara.Huge necropoleis of the dead, full of pyramids and temples eventually surrounded and dwarfed all the inhabited cities. Over hundreds of years, the necromancer Nagash waged a series of wars with the Nehekharans. His failure to dominate the region was bittersweet, as a final curse of epic proportions slew the populace and rendered the once-fertile kingdoms deserted.\n\nThrough the polluting side effects of Nagash's curse, the ancient Nehekharan magic and the manner of burial the Tomb Kings were born. Tomb Kings may command vast legions of Skeletons and Tomb Guard (the ancient bones of the long-dead inhabitants of Nehekhara), Ushabti, Bone Giants, Tomb Scorpions, undead Carrion birds, Screaming Skull Catapults, Liche Priests and even their personal Casket of Souls - to defend against any who would plunder their city or resting place.  
{IMPERIAL_CAMPAIGN_TIMURIDS_TITLE}Tomb Kings 
