¬ Generated by BinEditor v3.0
{ADVENTURE_CRUSADER_PENALTY_DESCR}The Knight Sigmar has decided to donate a small amount of money to your cause.
{ADVENTURE_CRUSADER_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}You cannot help the Knight Sigmar so his donation will be modest.
{ADVENTURE_CRUSADER_REWARD_DESCR}You have received a donation from Knight Sigmar
{ADVENTURE_CRUSADER_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}The more Knight Sigmar wins, the bigger your reward will be.
{ADVENTURE_CRUSADER_SOURCE}Knight Sigmar
{ASSASSINS_GUILD_MISSION_SOURCE}Assassins' Guild
{COUNCIL_MISSION_SOURCE}Council of Nobles
{EXPLORERS_GUILD_MISSION_SOURCE}Explorers' Guild
{FACTION_STANDING_PENALTY_DESCR}This faction thinks less of you.
{FACTION_STANDING_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}You will disappoint this faction.
{FACTION_STANDING_REWARD_DESCR}You have genuinely improved your relations with this faction.
{FACTION_STANDING_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}You will improve your relations with this faction.
{HUGE_PAPAL_STANDING_REWARD_DESCR}Your reputation with the Grand Theogonist has improved enormously.
{HUGE_PAPAL_STANDING_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}Your reputation with the Grand Theogonist will improve enormously. 
{LARGE_PAPAL_STANDING_PENALTY_DESCR}Your reputation with the Grand Theogonist has suffered enormously.
{LARGE_PAPAL_STANDING_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}Your reputation with the Grand Theogonist will suffer enormously. 
{LARGE_PAPAL_STANDING_REWARD_DESCR}Your reputation with the Grand Theogonist has improved significantly.
{LARGE_PAPAL_STANDING_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}Your reputation with the Grand Theogonist will improve significantly.
{MAJOR_EXPLORERS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_DESCR}The Explorers' Guild is very disappointed in you.
{MAJOR_EXPLORERS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}The Explorers' Guild will be very disappointed in you.
{MAJOR_EXPLORERS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_DESCR}The Explorers' Guild is very happy with you.
{MAJOR_EXPLORERS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}The Explorers' Guild will be very happy with you
{MASONS_GUILD_MISSION_SOURCE}Masons' Guild
{MED_PAPAL_STANDING_PENALTY_DESCR}Your reputation with the Grand Theogonist has suffered significantly.
{MED_PAPAL_STANDING_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}Your reputation with the Grand Theogonist will suffer significantly.
{MED_PAPAL_STANDING_REWARD_DESCR}Your reputation with the Grand Theogonist has improved.
{MED_PAPAL_STANDING_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}Your reputation with the Grand Theogonist will improve. 
{MERCHANTS_GUILD_MISSION_SOURCE}Merchants' Guild
{MIN_ASSASSINS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}The Assassins' Guild will be not impressed with your efforts.
{MIN_ASSASSINS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_DESCR}The Assassins' Guild appreciates your efforts.
{MIN_ASSASSINS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}The Assassins' Guild is far from impressed with your efforts.
{MIN_MERCHANTS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild is now disappointed with you.
{MIN_MERCHANTS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild will be disappointed with you.
{MIN_MERCHANTS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild is appreciative of your efforts.
{MIN_MERCHANTS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild will be appreciative of your efforts.
{MIN_THEOLOGIANS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_DESCR}The Theologians' Guild is now disappointed with you.
{MIN_THEOLOGIANS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}The Theologians' Guild will be disappointed with you.
{MIN_THEOLOGIANS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_DESCR}The Theologians' Guild is appreciative of your efforts.
{MIN_THEOLOGIANS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}The Theologians' Guild will be appreciative of your efforts.
{MIN_THIEFS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_DESCR}The Thieves' Guild is now disappointed with you.
{MIN_THIEFS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}The Thieves' Guild will be disappointed with you.
{MIN_THIEFS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_DESCR}The Thieves' Guild is appreciative of your efforts.
{MIN_THIEFS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}The Thieves' Guild will be appreciative of your efforts.
{MOD_MERCHANTS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild is impressed with you.
{MOD_MERCHANTS_GUILD_POINTS_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild will be impressed with you.
{MOD_MERCHANTS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild is thankful to you.
{MOD_MERCHANTS_GUILD_POINTS_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}The Merchants' Guild will be thankful to you.
{ORDER_COUNCIL_MISSION_SOURCE}Tip about the Order.
{PLACE_OF_WORSHIP_REWARD_DESCR}The Masons' Guild has built you a place of worship.
{PLACE_OF_WORSHIP_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}The Masons' Guild have offered to construct place of worship for you.
{POPE_MISSION_SOURCE}The Grand Theogonist
{SMALL_PAPAL_STANDING_PENALTY_DESCR}Your reputation with the Grand Theogonist is not as high as it once was.
{SMALL_PAPAL_STANDING_PENALTY_PRE_DESCR}Your reputation with the Grand Theogonist will not be as high as it once was.
{SMALL_PAPAL_STANDING_REWARD_DESCR}Your reputation with the Grand Theogonist has improved slightly.
{SMALL_PAPAL_STANDING_REWARD_PRE_DESCR}Your reputation with the Grand Theogonist will improve slightly.
{VNV_ADORED_BY_POPE_DESCR}The Grand Theogonist considers your leader one of his closest allies.
{VNV_ADORED_BY_POPE_PRE_DESCR}Your leader will become one of the Grand Theogonist's closest allies. 
{VNV_POPES_ENFORCER_DESCR}Your leader is the steel gauntlet of the Grand Theogonist's will.
{VNV_POPES_ENFORCER_PRE_DESCR}Your leader will become the steel gauntlet of the Grand Theogonist's will.
{adventure_crusader_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This Order allied itself with Kislev.
{adventure_crusader_EXPIRY_DEATH}The Knight Sigmar is dead - a great shame for all who followed him.
{adventure_crusader_FAILURE}You did not help enough. The Knight Sigmar returned home and left some change left.
{adventure_crusader_PROPOSAL}Help the newly arrived Knight Sigmar in fulfilling his sacred vows and he will leave a substantial donation.
{adventure_crusader_SUCCESS}Knights of Sigmar were successful. The left generous donations in gratitude for the help and returned home.
{adventure_crusader_TITLE}Assist the Knight Sigmar
{annex_settlement_EXPIRY_DEATH}The faction you were to treaty with has been vanquished. There is no longer a need for you to send a diplomat to them. 
{annex_settlement_EXPIRY_LOST}Another faction has taken this settlement. There is no longer a need for you to send a diplomat to this faction.
{annex_settlement_FAILURE}You have failed to convince our rivals to hand over this settlement; the Council is greatly disappointed at this turn of events.
{annex_settlement_PROPOSAL}By rights, this settlement should be under our authority. It is a mockery for it to be held by our rivals. The Council suggests you send a diplomat and attempt to have them to hand it over. You may be able to offer them a settlement that is less valuable to us in exchange.
{annex_settlement_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully convinced this faction to hand over land that is rightfully ours; the Council is much impressed by your obvious authority.
{annex_settlement_TITLE}Annex Settlement
{assassinate_captain_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This man has become our ally; it is no longer necessary to remove him.
{assassinate_captain_EXPIRY_DEATH}Your target has died; you are no longer required to assassinate him.
{assassinate_captain_EXPIRY_HIDING}Your target has gone into hiding; you are no longer required to assassinate him.
{assassinate_captain_FAILURE}You have failed to assassinate this individual; the Council assumes this must be part of your great plan.
{assassinate_captain_PROPOSAL}This miscreant's demise would please a great many people, not to mention make smoother our path to success. The Council suggests you send an assassin to hasten this man's journey into the next world. 
{assassinate_captain_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully assassinated this individual; the Council is impressed by your ruthlessness.
{assassinate_captain_TITLE}Assassination Mission
{assassinate_cardinal_EXPIRY_DEATH}As this man has died, the Grand Theogonist has no need for you to 'deal' with him.
{assassinate_cardinal_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}You have been excommunicated, the Grand Theogonist no longer trusts you with this important duty.
{assassinate_cardinal_EXPIRY_HIDING}This man cannot be found, the Grand Theogonist has no need for you to 'deal' with him.
{assassinate_cardinal_FAILURE}The Grand Theogonist is disquieted by your failure to 'deal' with this man.
{assassinate_cardinal_PROPOSAL}This man's profanity and disrespect has deeply distressed the Grand Theogonist. He assures you that Sigmar himself will smile upon you if you can deal with this delicate matter (kill him!).
{assassinate_cardinal_SUCCESS}You have done the Church of Sigmar a great favour, and much pleased the Grand Theogonist by successfully assassinating this Cardinal.
{assassinate_cardinal_TITLE}Assassinate Theogonist 
{assassinate_general_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This man has become our ally; it is no longer necessary to remove him.
{assassinate_general_EXPIRY_DEATH}Your target has died; you are no longer required to assassinate him.
{assassinate_general_EXPIRY_HIDING}Your target has gone into hiding; you are no longer required to assassinate him.
{assassinate_general_FAILURE}You have failed to assassinate this individual; the Council assumes this must be part of your great plan.
{assassinate_general_PROPOSAL}This miscreant's demise would please a great many people, not to mention make smoother our path to success. The Council suggests you send an assassin to hasten this man's journey into the next world. 
{assassinate_general_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully assassinated this individual; the Council is impressed by your ruthlessness.
{assassinate_general_TITLE}Assassination Mission
{assassinate_witch_heretic_EXPIRY_DEATH}The Grand Theogonist has no need for you to assassinate this person, as they have perished.
{assassinate_witch_heretic_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated; the Grand Theogonist does not trust the likes of you to uphold the Word of Sigmar. You are no longer charged with the assassination of this person.
{assassinate_witch_heretic_EXPIRY_HIDING}The Grand Theogonist has no need for you to assassinate this person, as they cannot be found.
{assassinate_witch_heretic_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Grand Theogonist by failing to assassinate this blasphemer as asked.
{assassinate_witch_heretic_PROPOSAL}This blasphemer is a stain on the world and the Grand Theogonist wishes you to cleanse it. Assassinate this person immediately!
{assassinate_witch_heretic_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Grand Theogonist by successfully assassinating this blasphemer, and thus making the world more pleasing to His eye.
{assassinate_witch_heretic_TITLE}Assassinate the heretic
{blockade_distant_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This faction has become an ally; you are no longer required to blockade this port.
{blockade_distant_EXPIRY_BLOCKADED}It appears this port is already blockaded; you are no longer required to blockade it.
{blockade_distant_EXPIRY_SETTLEMENT_TAKEN}This port has been taken; you are no longer expected to blockade it.
{blockade_distant_FAILURE}You have not blockaded this port, the Council bows to your infinitely wiser decision.
{blockade_distant_PROPOSAL}It is time we apply pressure upon our foes. Sending a fleet to blockade this port for at least 1 turns will not only hurt our enemy, but it will fill our coffers.
{blockade_distant_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully blockaded this port; the Council applauds your decisiveness.
{blockade_distant_TITLE}Blockade Port 
{blockade_heretic_EXPIRY_BLOCKADED}This port is already blockaded, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_heretic_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated. You are no longer trusted to blockade this port.
{blockade_heretic_EXPIRY_RECOMMUNICATED}As this faction has returned to the fold and been reconciled, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_heretic_EXPIRY_SETTLEMENT_TAKEN}This settlement has been taken, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_heretic_FAILURE}You have let down the Grand Theogonist and Sigmar by unsuccessfully blockading this port.
{blockade_heretic_PROPOSAL}The Grand Theogonist wishes you to blockade this port for at least 3 turns. Such chastisement will serve to both punish these heretics and stop their unholy rot from spreading to the faithful.
{blockade_heretic_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Grand Theogonist and Sigmar by successfully blockading this port.
{blockade_heretic_TITLE}Blockade Port
{blockade_islam_EXPIRY_BLOCKADED}This port is already blockaded, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_islam_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated. You are no longer trusted to blockade this port.
{blockade_islam_EXPIRY_RECOMMUNICATED}As this faction has come to the fold, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_islam_EXPIRY_SETTLEMENT_TAKEN}This settlement has been taken, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_islam_FAILURE}You have let down the Grand Theogonist and Sigmar by unsuccessfully blockading this port.
{blockade_islam_PROPOSAL}The Grand Theogonist wishes you to blockade this port for at least 3 turns. Such chastisement will serve to weaken these enemies of Sigmar.
{blockade_islam_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Grand Theogonist and Sigmar by successfully blockading this port.
{blockade_islam_TITLE}Blockade Port
{blockade_moderate_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This faction has become an ally; you are no longer required to blockade this port.
{blockade_moderate_EXPIRY_BLOCKADED}It appears this port is already blockaded; you are no longer required to blockade it.
{blockade_moderate_EXPIRY_SETTLEMENT_TAKEN}This port has been taken; you are no longer expected to blockade it.
{blockade_moderate_FAILURE}You have not blockaded this port, the Council bows to your infinitely wiser decision.
{blockade_moderate_PROPOSAL}It is time we apply pressure upon our foes. Sending a fleet to blockade this port for at least 2 turns will not only hurt our enemy, but it will fill our coffers.
{blockade_moderate_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully blockaded this port; the Council applauds your decisiveness.
{blockade_moderate_TITLE}Blockade Port 
{blockade_pagan_EXPIRY_BLOCKADED}This port is already blockaded, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_pagan_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated. You are no longer trusted to blockade this port.
{blockade_pagan_EXPIRY_RECOMMUNICATED}As this faction has come to the fold, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_pagan_EXPIRY_SETTLEMENT_TAKEN}This settlement has been taken, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{blockade_pagan_FAILURE}You have let down the Grand Theogonist and Sigmar by unsuccessfully blockading this port.
{blockade_pagan_PROPOSAL}The Grand Theogonist wishes you to blockade this port for at least 3 turns. Such chastisement will serve to both punish these heathens and stop their unholy rot from spreading to the faithful.
{blockade_pagan_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Grand Theogonist and Sigmar by successfully blockading this port.
{blockade_pagan_TITLE}Blockade Port
{break_alliance_EXPIRY_DEATH}As this faction has perished, you are no longer required to break your alliance with them.
{break_alliance_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated. You are no longer required to break your alliance with this faction.
{break_alliance_EXPIRY_RECOMMUNICATED}As this faction has returned to the fold and been reconciled, you are no longer required to break your alliance with them.
{break_alliance_FAILURE}The Grand Theogonist can only wonder what went wrong; you have disappointed the him by failing to break your alliance with this faction. 
{break_alliance_PROPOSAL}In uncertain times like these, it is important to know who one's true allies are. The Grand Theogonist demands you break your alliance with this profane and heretical faction to prove your loyalty.
{break_alliance_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Grand Theogonist and proven your loyalty by successfully breaking your alliance with this faction.
{break_alliance_TITLE}Break Alliance
{castle_chapel_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated; the Grand Theogonist cares naught what you build in this castle.
{castle_chapel_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this castle, you are no longer charged with building a Chapel there.
{castle_chapel_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Grand Theogonist by failing to build a Chapel in this castle, and thus hampering the proper worship of Sigmar in this castle.
{castle_chapel_PROPOSAL}It has come to the Grand Theogonist's attention that this castle is bereft of a proper place of worship. He wishes you to build a Chapel in this castle.
{castle_chapel_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Grand Theogonist by successfully building a Chapel in this castle, and thus propagating the proper worship of Sigmar in this castle.
{castle_chapel_TITLE}Build a Chapel
{castle_small_chapel_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated; the Grand Theogonist cares naught what you build in this castle.
{castle_small_chapel_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this castle, you are no longer charged with building a Small Chapel there.
{castle_small_chapel_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Grand Theogonist by failing to build a Small Chapel in this castle, and thus hampering the proper worship of Sigmar in this castle.
{castle_small_chapel_PROPOSAL}It has come to the Grand Theogonist's attention that this castle is bereft of a proper place of worship. He wishes you to build a Small Chapel in this castle.
{castle_small_chapel_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Grand Theogonist by successfully building a Small Chapel in this castle, and thus propagating the proper worship of Sigmar in this castle.
{castle_small_chapel_TITLE}Build a Small Chapel
{cease_hostilities_EXPIRY_DEATH}The Grand Theogonist is no longer concerned about the fate of this faction as it has been eliminated.
{cease_hostilities_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless and ignoble faction has been excommunicated, the Sigmarite Church no longer expects such as you to listen to the request of the Grand Theogonist.
{cease_hostilities_EXPIRY_TARGET_EXCOMMUNICATED}As this faction has been excommunicated, it matters little how much of their faithless blood you spill. You are no longer charged with ceasing hostilities with this faction.
{cease_hostilities_FAILURE}You have greatly saddened the Grand Theogonist by failing to cease hostilities with your fellow Sigmarites, and continuing to shed the blood of your brother.
{cease_hostilities_PROPOSAL}The Grand Theogonist demands that you stop shedding the blood of your fellow Sigmarites. Cease hostilities against this faction immediately and do not carry out hostile acts for the duration of this mission.
{cease_hostilities_SUCCESS}You have greatly pleased the Grand Theogonist by refraining from hostile actions against your fellow Sigmarites. He only hopes this newfound peace will last.
{cease_hostilities_TITLE}Cease Hostilities
{city_abbey_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated; the Grand Theogonist cares naught what you build in this city.
{city_abbey_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this city, you are no longer charged with building an Abbey there.
{city_abbey_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Grand Theogonist by failing to build an Abbey in this city, and thus hampering the proper worship of Sigmar in this city.
{city_abbey_PROPOSAL}It has come to the Grand Theogonist's attention that this settlement is bereft of a proper place of worship. He wishes you to build an Abbey in this settlement.
{city_abbey_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Grand Theogonist by successfully building an Abbey in this city, and thus propagating the proper worship of Sigmar in this city.
{city_abbey_TITLE}Build an Abbey
{city_cathedral_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated; the Grand Theogonist cares naught what you build in this city.
{city_cathedral_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this city, you are no longer charged with building a Cathedral there.
{city_cathedral_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Grand Theogonist by failing to build a Cathedral in this city, and thus hampering the proper worship of Sigmar in this city.
{city_cathedral_PROPOSAL}It has come to His Holiness's attention that this city is bereft of a proper place of worship. The Grand Theogonist wishes you to build a Cathedral in this city.
{city_cathedral_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Grand Theogonist by successfully building a Cathedral in this city, and thus propagating the proper worship of Sigmar in this city.
{city_cathedral_TITLE}Build a Cathedral
{city_huge_cathedral_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated; the Grand Theogonist cares naught what you build in this city.
{city_huge_cathedral_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this city, you are no longer charged with building a Huge Cathedral there.
{city_huge_cathedral_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Grand Theogonist by failing to build a Huge Cathedral in this city, and thus hampering the proper worship of Sigmar in this city.
{city_huge_cathedral_PROPOSAL}It has come to the Grand Theogonist's attention that this city is bereft of a proper place of worship. He wishes you to build a Huge Cathedral in this city.
{city_huge_cathedral_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Grand Theogonist by successfully building a Huge Cathedral in this city, and thus propagating the proper worship of Sigmar in this city.
{city_huge_cathedral_TITLE}Build a Huge Cathedral
{city_small_church_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated; the Grand Theogonist cares naught what you build in this city.
{city_small_church_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this city, you are no longer charged with building a Small Church there.
{city_small_church_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Grand Theogonist by failing to build a Small Church in this city, and thus hampering the proper worship of Sigmar in this city.
{city_small_church_PROPOSAL}It has come to the Grand Theogonist's attention that this city is bereft of a proper place of worship. He wishes you to build a Small Church in this city.
{city_small_church_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Grand Theogonist by successfully building a Small Church in this city, and thus propagating the proper worship of Sigmar in this city.
{city_small_church_TITLE}Build a Small Church
{convert_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your ungodly faction has been excommunicated. One cannot expect a nest of vipers to bring forward the lambs. You are no longer charged with converting the people to the 'one true faith. 
{convert_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Grand Theogonist by failing to convert sufficient people in this settlement.
{convert_PROPOSAL}The Grand Theogonist sees that the unbelievers in this settlement are clouding the judgement of the righteous. Send a priest to convert at least %d %% of the population to Sigmarism.
{convert_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Grand Theogonist by successfully spreading the word and converting more believers in this settlement.
{convert_TITLE}Spread the Word of Sigmar
{council_blockade_port_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This faction has become an ally; you are no longer required to blockade this port.
{council_blockade_port_EXPIRY_BLOCKADED}It appears this port is already blockaded; you are no longer required to blockade it.
{council_blockade_port_EXPIRY_SETTLEMENT_TAKEN}This port has been taken; you are no longer expected to blockade it.
{council_blockade_port_FAILURE}You have not blockaded this port, the Council bows to your infinitely wiser decision.
{council_blockade_port_PROPOSAL}It is time we apply pressure upon our foes. Sending a fleet to blockade this port for at least 3 turns will not only hurt our enemy, but it will fill our coffers.
{council_blockade_port_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully blockaded this port; the Council applauds your decisiveness.
{council_blockade_port_TITLE}Blockade Port 
{council_marry_princess_EXPIRY_GENERAL_DEATH}Alas this marriage can never be, the general has died, and nearly left our Princess a widow.
{council_marry_princess_EXPIRY_PRINCESS_DEATH}Alas, the poor Princess has died; we must call the marriage off.
{council_marry_princess_EXPIRY_PRINCESS_RETIRED}Our Princess is now too old to marry; her time would be better spent on more solitary and contemplative pursuits. The marriage is off.
{council_marry_princess_EXPIRY_TARGET_MARRIED}Love can be a fickle thing, and this lord is twice such, he has married another. The marriage to our Princess is off.
{council_marry_princess_FAILURE}You have not arranged the marriage this Council recommended. The Council bows to your greater judgement in these matters.
{council_marry_princess_FAILURE_PRINCESS_MARRIED}Love can be a fickle thing, it seems our Princess has married another, the original marriage is off.
{council_marry_princess_PROPOSAL}Lord %S has been beguiled by the lovely Princess %S. He is willing to pay a handsome dowry for her hand in marriage. The Council recommends you arrange this marriage as soon as possible.
{council_marry_princess_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully arranged the marriage we recommended. This union is sure to bear fruit in time.
{council_marry_princess_TITLE}A Proposal for the Princess's Hand
{council_take_rebel_settlement_EXPIRY_LOST}Another has taken this Rebel settlement. You are no longer required to take it.
{council_take_rebel_settlement_FAILURE}It appears you have decided against this Council's advice by not taking this Rebel settlement, the Council can only assume this is yet another sudden turn in your labyrinth-like plan.
{council_take_rebel_settlement_PROPOSAL}Our great nation appears weak to tolerate such insolence from these rebels. The Council recommends you capture this rebel settlement and assert your authority.
{council_take_rebel_settlement_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully taken this Rebel settlement and displayed our strength to all.
{council_take_rebel_settlement_TITLE}Take Rebel Settlement
{council_take_settlement_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This faction has become an ally; you are no longer required to take it.
{council_take_settlement_EXPIRY_LOST}Another has taken this settlement.
{council_take_settlement_FAILURE}You have failed to take this settlement; perhaps you felt it was not the right time to expand our borders?
{council_take_settlement_PROPOSAL}It is time to further our great empire by extending our borders. The Council suggests you take this settlement for the glory of the nation.
{council_take_settlement_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully taken this settlement, and extended our Empire.
{council_take_settlement_TITLE}Take Settlement
{crusade_active_PROPOSAL}The Grand Theogonist has called for a holy Crusade to this settlement. It is time for righteous steel and arms strengthened by faith to free this part of the Empire's land from its enemies.
{crusade_active_TARGET_PROPOSAL}It is a nightmarish day for your people that inhabit this settlement, for the Grand Theogonist has called a holy Crusade against it! The seemingly endless armies of the Empire will soon be marching to lay siege to the walls... Make peace with the the Grand Theogonist, or make ready to defend it!
{crusade_active_TITLE}A Holy Crusade
{gift_from_council_PROPOSAL}The Council are greatly impressed by your leadership and would like you to accept this humble offering as a token of past and future endeavours.
{gift_from_council_TITLE}A Gift from the Council
{gift_from_pope_PROPOSAL}The Grand Theogonist has noticed your faithful dedication to the Sigmarite Church and is pleased to grant you this gift.
{gift_from_pope_TITLE}A Gift from the the Grand Theogonist
{give_ancillary_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Grand Theogonist by coveting this relic and thus failing to hand it over to him.
{give_ancillary_PROPOSAL}The Grand Theogonist has heard of your retrieval of this wondrous holy relic and sends his congratulations. You must hand over this relic so that it may reside with him, as is proper.
{give_ancillary_SUCCESS}The Grand Theogonist sends you his gratitude for the rightful return of this holy relic to the Sigmarite Church.
{give_ancillary_TITLE}Give Relic to the Grand Theogonist
{give_cash_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Grand Theogonist with your selfishness, by failing to "donate" sufficient gold to him.
{give_cash_PROPOSAL}Sigmar favours he who is generous. Make a "donation" of at least %d florins to the the Grand Theogonist. 
{give_cash_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Grand Theogonist with your generous "donation". Blessed is he who gives.
{give_cash_TITLE}Give a "donation" to the Grand Theogonist
{guild_acquisition_EXPIRY_DEATH}It appears this merchant has perished; we no longer need to remove him.
{guild_acquisition_EXPIRY_HIDING}It appears this merchant has gone into hiding; we no longer need to remove him. 
{guild_acquisition_FAILURE}You have failed to complete the desired acquisition; the Guild is disappointed with this outcome. 
{guild_acquisition_PROPOSAL}There is lucrative trade to be had here, but first we must deal with the opposition. The Guild recommends you send your merchant to make an acquisition of this merchants' trade. 
{guild_acquisition_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully made the acquisition; the Guild owes you its thanks.
{guild_acquisition_TITLE}Mercantile Acquisition
{guild_build_PROPOSAL}In recognition of your past aid and support to the Mason's Guild, the masons will build a place of worship in your honour, so that the faithful may gather.
{guild_build_TITLE}A Gift from the Mason's Guild
{guild_recruit_agent_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this settlement, the Guild no longer expects you to train an assassin there.
{guild_recruit_agent_FAILURE}You have failed to train an assassin; the Guild is disappointed with this result.
{guild_recruit_agent_PROPOSAL}Sometimes a single drop of poison or one knife in the dark can achieve what an entire army cannot. The Guild requests that you train an assassin in this settlement.
{guild_recruit_agent_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully trained an assassin, the Guild is very pleased.
{guild_recruit_agent_TITLE}Train Assassin
{guild_recruit_merchant_EXPIRY_LIMIT}It appears there are sufficient merchants for the time being. The Guild no longer requires you to recruit a merchant.
{guild_recruit_merchant_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this settlement, the Guild no longer expects you to train a Merchant there.
{guild_recruit_merchant_FAILURE}You have failed to train a Merchant; the Guild is disappointed with this result.
{guild_recruit_merchant_PROPOSAL}Three things are required to make war and conquest; gold, gold and more gold. The Guild requests that you train a Merchant in this settlement.
{guild_recruit_merchant_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully trained a Merchant, the Guild is very pleased.
{guild_recruit_merchant_TITLE}Train Merchant
{guild_recruit_priest_EXPIRY_LIMIT}It appears there are enough of Sigmar's soldiers for the time being. The Guild no longer requires you to recruit a priest. 
{guild_recruit_priest_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this settlement, the Guild no longer expects you to train a Priest there.
{guild_recruit_priest_FAILURE}You have failed to train a Priest; the Guild is disappointed with this result.
{guild_recruit_priest_PROPOSAL}The Holy word requires another soldier of faith. The Guild requests that you train a Priest in this settlement.
{guild_recruit_priest_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully trained a Priest, the Guild is very pleased.
{guild_recruit_priest_TITLE}Train Priest
{guild_recruit_spy_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this settlement, the Guild no longer expects you to train a Spy there.
{guild_recruit_spy_FAILURE}You have failed to train a Spy; the Guild is disappointed with this result.
{guild_recruit_spy_PROPOSAL}Sometimes a little bit of information is worth a dozen armies. The Guild requests that you train a Spy in this settlement.
{guild_recruit_spy_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully trained a Spy, the Guild is very pleased.
{guild_recruit_spy_TITLE}Train Spy
{guild_take_settlement_EXPIRY_ALLIED}An alliance has been forged with this settlement, the Guild no longer requires you to take it.
{guild_take_settlement_EXPIRY_LOST}Another has taken this settlement, the Guild no longer requires you to take it.
{guild_take_settlement_FAILURE}You have failed to take this settlement; the Guild is disappointed with this lack of progress.
{guild_take_settlement_PROPOSAL}The Guild's interests would be better looked after if this settlement were to become part of your empire. The Guild requests that you take this settlement.
{guild_take_settlement_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully taken this settlement; the Guild owes you its thanks.
{guild_take_settlement_TITLE}Take Settlement
{guild_trade_agreement_EXPIRY_DEATH}This faction has been vanquished; a trade agreement with them is no longer possible.
{guild_trade_agreement_EXPIRY_WAR}These fools have chosen war with us rather than peaceful trade. So be it, a trade agreement with them is no longer possible. 
{guild_trade_agreement_FAILURE}You have not obtained a trade agreement with this faction; the Guild is disappointed with this outcome.
{guild_trade_agreement_PROPOSAL}We are losing lucrative trade opportunities, as we currently have no trade Agreement with this faction. The Guild would like you to obtain a trade agreement with these people.
{guild_trade_agreement_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully obtained a Trade Agreement with this faction; the Guild owes you its thanks.
{guild_trade_agreement_TITLE}Obtain Trade Agreement
{jihad_active_PROPOSAL}An army is moving on this settlement to clean away the hated enemy. It is time to dispense rightful anger upon these fools.
{jihad_active_TARGET_PROPOSAL}A great Shaman has called for warriors to take up arms against your people and descend upon this settlement! The willingness of the soldiers' to die for such a cause make this one of the most terrifying perils the people of this place will ever face... Ensure they are prepared.
{jihad_active_TITLE}A Waaagh!
{join_crusade_CHARACTER_PROPOSAL}The Grand Theogonist has requested that %S demonstrate his faith and personally join the Crusade.
{join_crusade_EXPIRED_DEATH}Your General has died. As a result, you can no longer join the Crusade.
{join_crusade_EXPIRED_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated. You have no place amongst the worthy; you can no longer join the Crusade.
{join_crusade_EXPIRED_FINISHED}The Crusade has ended; you can no longer join. 
{join_crusade_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Grand Theogonist by not meeting your obligations to Sigmar and failing to join the Crusade.
{join_crusade_HEIR_TITLE}Your Heir must join the Crusade.
{join_crusade_LEADER_TITLE}Your Leader must join the Crusade.
{join_crusade_PROPOSAL}The Grand Theogonist has called a holy Crusade, and he has sent the call to arms to all devoted Sigmarite factions. You must create a Crusading army within the time limit to take part.
{join_crusade_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Grand Theogonist and proven your faith by successfully joining the Crusade. 
{join_crusade_TITLE}Join the Crusade
{kill_crusader_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This Knight is now our new ally. He should be left untouched.
{kill_crusader_EXPIRY_DEATH}Your incompetence is clearly visible. You have not eliminated this man.
{kill_crusader_EXPIRY_HIDING}It is not possible to locate this man. He went into hiding like a coward. The mission is over.
{kill_crusader_FAILURE}Your incompetence is clearly visible. You have not eliminated this man.
{kill_crusader_PROPOSAL}This character is a direct threat to our nation. He must be eliminated at all costs.
{kill_crusader_SUCCESS}You are succesful at helping this man ending his poor life.
{kill_crusader_TITLE}Kill the Knight Sigmar
{papal_blockade_port_EXPIRY_BLOCKADED}This port is already blockaded, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{papal_blockade_port_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated. You are no longer trusted to blockade this port.
{papal_blockade_port_EXPIRY_RECOMMUNICATED}As this faction has returned to the fold and been reconciled, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{papal_blockade_port_EXPIRY_SETTLEMENT_TAKEN}This settlement has been taken, you are no longer charged to blockade this port.
{papal_blockade_port_FAILURE}You have let down the Grand Theogonist and Sigmar by unsuccessfully blockading this port.
{papal_blockade_port_PROPOSAL}The Grand Theogonist only wishes that this man be returned to the fold. Perhaps cutting his income will make him see the light. Use your fleet to blockade this port for at least 3 turns.
{papal_blockade_port_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Grand Theogonist and Sigmar by successfully blockading this port.
{papal_blockade_port_TITLE}Blockade Port
{papal_build_church_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your faithless faction has been excommunicated; the Grand Theogonist cares naught what you build in this settlement.
{papal_build_church_EXPIRY_LOST}As you have lost this settlement, you are no longer charged with building a church there.
{papal_build_church_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Grand Theogonist by failing to build a church in this settlement, and thus hampering the proper worship of Sigmar in this settlement.
{papal_build_church_PROPOSAL}It has come to the Grand Theogonist's attention that this settlement is bereft of a proper place of worship. He wishes you to build a church in this settlement.
{papal_build_church_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Grand Theogonist by successfully building a church in this settlement, and thus propagating the proper worship of Sigmar in this settlement.
{papal_build_church_TITLE}Build a Church
{recruit_priest_EXPIRY_EXCOMMUNICATED}Your worthless faction has been excommunicated, a priest from such a flock would be at best worthless. You are no longer charged with recruiting a priest.
{recruit_priest_EXPIRY_LIMIT}It appears there are enough of Sigmar's servants for the time being. The Guild no longer requires you to recruit a priest. 
{recruit_priest_EXPIRY_LOST}You have lost this settlement, you are no longer charged with recruiting a priest.
{recruit_priest_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Grand Theogonist by failing to recruit a priest, and thus hampering his holy work.
{recruit_priest_PROPOSAL}The dwindling number of Sigmarites in this settlement reflects poorly on the Church of Sigmar. Recruit a priest in this settlement to convert more people.
{recruit_priest_SUCCESS}You have pleased the Grand Theogonist by successfully recruiting a priest, and thus creating yet another vessel for Sigmar's Word.
{recruit_priest_TITLE}Recruit a Priest
{regicide_EXPIRY_DEATH}My 'noble' father has perished; you are no longer required to 'intervene'.
{regicide_EXPIRY_HIDING}My father has gone to ground like the mole he is, you are no longer required to 'intervene'. 
{regicide_EXPIRY_SOURCE_DEATH}Наследник трона отошел в мир иной, и вам более не нужно исполнять его жестокие приказы. Но неужели все ваши труды окажутся напрасными? В конце концов, нет ничего зазорного в устранении очередного соперника...
{regicide_FAILURE}You have failed to deal with my wretched father as I requested, I will not forget this.
{regicide_PROPOSAL}My father is naught but a simpering fool. If left to rule he will bring only ruin to what should be my empire. Kill him so that I may lead my empire to greatness, and our empires will rule the world side by side as brothers. I am willing to generously 'recompense' you for your troubles.
{regicide_SUCCESS}You have my endless gratitude; you have done both my people and myself a great favour. Your deed may go unsung but it will not go unrewarded, nor forgotten.
{regicide_TITLE}Regicide
{reinforce_region_EXPIRY_LOST}It is too late, the settlement is lost! It can no longer be reinforced by our forces.
{reinforce_region_FAILURE}You have failed to reinforce this region and left it vulnerable to attack, the Council hopes this is all part of some master strategy.
{reinforce_region_PROPOSAL}This region is the frontier to our enemies, but is undermanned and vulnerable to attack. The Council suggests you increase our forces here by at least 4 units.
{reinforce_region_SUCCESS}Well done, you have successfully reinforced this region against attacks from our foes, the Council is comforted by your wisdom.
{reinforce_region_TITLE}Reinforce Region
{return_papal_settlement_FAILURE}You have disappointed the Grand Theogonist by failing to return his lands to the Empire.
{return_papal_settlement_PROPOSAL}The Grand Theogonist has requested that you return his lands to the Empire. His Holiness will be greatly in your debt if you can see fit to return his home city.
{return_papal_settlement_SUCCESS}You have greatly pleased the Grand Theogonist by successfully returning his lands to the Empire.
{return_papal_settlement_TITLE}Return the Grand Theogonist's lands to the Empire.
{send_emissary_EXPIRY_DEATH}The faction you were to meet with has been vanquished. There is no longer a need for you to send a diplomat to them.
{send_emissary_FAILURE}You have failed to establish diplomatic relations with these people, the Council hopes this is for the best.
{send_emissary_PROPOSAL}There are foreigners almost at our very gates and we know very little of them. The Council suggests you send an emissary to this faction and initiate diplomatic relations.
{send_emissary_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully established diplomatic relations with these people; the Council admires the ease with which you handle diplomacy.
{send_emissary_TITLE}Send Emissary
{steal_general_EXPIRY_GENERAL_DEATH}Alas this marriage can never be, the general has died, and nearly left our Princess a widow.
{steal_general_EXPIRY_PRINCESS_DEATH}Alas, the poor Princess has died; we must call the marriage off.
{steal_general_EXPIRY_PRINCESS_RETIRED}Our Princess is now too old to marry; her time would be better spent on more solitary and contemplative pursuits. The marriage is off.
{steal_general_EXPIRY_TARGET_MARRIED}Love can be a fickle thing, and this lord is twice such, he has married another. The marriage to our Princess is off.
{steal_general_FAILURE}You have not arranged the marriage this Council recommended. The Council bows to your greater judgement in these matters.
{steal_general_FAILURE_PRINCESS_MARRIED}Love can be a fickle thing, it seems our Princess has married another, the original marriage is off.
{steal_general_PROPOSAL}Lord %S has been beguiled by the lovely Princess %S. He is willing to pay a handsome dowry for her hand in marriage. The Council recommends you arrange this marriage as soon as possible.
{steal_general_SUCCESS}Congratulations, you have successfully arranged the marriage we recommended. This union is sure to bear fruit in time.
{steal_general_TITLE}A Proposal for the Princess's Hand
{teutonic_assassinate_general_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This character has become our ally, and killing him is not required.
{teutonic_assassinate_general_EXPIRY_DEATH}This character is dead, and killing him is not required.
{teutonic_assassinate_general_EXPIRY_HIDING}This character has hide himself, and killing him is not required.
{teutonic_assassinate_general_EXPIRY_RELIGION}This hero realized error of his beliefs and renounced paganism, killing him is not required.
{teutonic_assassinate_general_FAILURE}You did not remove this man. The Council will consider this failure as a part of your grand design...
{teutonic_assassinate_general_PROPOSAL}This man is a living abomination - a non-believer. He must be put to the sword.
{teutonic_assassinate_general_SUCCESS}You have been succesful. Your devotion to Sigmar is noted.
{teutonic_assassinate_general_TITLE}Murder pagan commander
{teutonic_assassinate_priest_EXPIRY_ALLIED}This character has become our ally. His removal has lost all meaning.
{teutonic_assassinate_priest_EXPIRY_DEATH}This character is no longer dangerous to our people. There is no need to kill him.
{teutonic_assassinate_priest_EXPIRY_HIDING}This character is nowhere to find. The quest for his head had ended.
{teutonic_assassinate_priest_FAILURE}A simple man escaped you. How was that even possible?
{teutonic_assassinate_priest_PROPOSAL}This character is dangerous for our people - he tests our servants' faith. He must be dealt with.
{teutonic_assassinate_priest_SUCCESS}You are commended gor your dealing with this man.
{teutonic_assassinate_priest_TITLE}Murder the Priest
{teutonic_captureconvert_EXPIRY_ALLIED} These people became our allies. You don't have to capture their settlement.
{teutonic_captureconvert_EXPIRY_LOST}This settlement was captured by other people.
{teutonic_captureconvert_EXPIRY_RELIGION}The people of this power have realized how wrong their actions were, and they embarked on the path of truth. You don't need to capture this settlement.
{teutonic_captureconvert_FAILURE}You did not capture this settlement. Do you think you are better than the Grand Theogonist himself?
{teutonic_captureconvert_PROPOSAL}Great Theogonist wants you to  capture this settlement and bring its inhabitants to his worshippers.
{teutonic_captureconvert_SUCCESS}The seeds of conversion bring their first fruit.
{teutonic_captureconvert_TITLE} capture and convert the settlement's residents to the true faith.
{teutonic_convert_FAILURE}How can you command a nation if you are unable to show the light of true faith in this small settlement?
{teutonic_convert_PROPOSAL} Now, this settlement is in your power. Hurry up to draw his people into the true faith! Sigmarists must be at least% d%% of the population.
{teutonic_convert_SUCCESS} His Holiness is happy - you are fulfilling his wishes.
{teutonic_convert_TITLE} Appeal to the true faith.
