¬ Generated by BinEditor v3.0
{Author_1}Captain Strasse, sole survivor of the Siege of Norbsteim
{Author_2}Captain Strasse, sole survivor of the Siege of Norbsteim
{Author_3}Sergeant Morser, defending Nuln during Waaagh! Grom
{Author_4}Lord of the Freistadt of Akendorf
{Author_5}Burgermeister Nusbaum, at the Siege of Norbsteim
{Author_6}Part of "The Song of the Creator", sung once a decade by the Asur
{Author_7}Part of "The Song of the Creator", sung once a decade by the Asur
{Author_8}Part of "The Song of the Creator", sung once a decade by the Asur
{Author_9}Part of "The Song of the Creator", sung once a decade by the Asur
{Author_10}Part of "The Song of the Creator", sung once a decade by the Asur
{Author_11}Unthwe Windrider, White Lion and Herald of the Phoenix King
{Author_12}Unknown, describing Aenarion the Defender
{Author_13}Belannaer, Loremaster of Saphery to Eltharion, Warden of Yvresse
{Author_14}Laelinn, Reaver Knight of the Asur
{Author_15}Herwig Algnar describing the Phoenix Guard, from his book "A Man among the Elves"
{Author_16}From the Battle Hymn of Tiranoc
{Author_17}From the Battle Hymn of Tiranoc
{Author_18}From the Battle Hymn of Tiranoc
{Author_19}Eolaran Greyhawk, Sea Master of Lothern
{Author_20}Nils Valera, Agitator
{Author_21}Hanskarl Denk, Sylvanian
{Author_22}Malekith, The Witch King of Naggaroth
{Author_23}Skarloc, Shadow Sentinel of Athel Loren
{Author_24}Magnus the Pious
{Author_25}Alexei Zucharov
{Author_26}Grand Theogonist Kazgar XIV, at the funeral of Magnus the Pious
{Author_27}Western Merchants about dealings with the Kislevites
{Author_28}Kaspar von Velten, Ambassador of the Empire to Ice Queen Tzarina Katarin
{Author_29}Ernst Traugott, Templar Witch Hunter
{Author_30}Witch Hunter Motto
{Author_31}Siege Engineer Uwe Diamondscar at the siege of the goblin fort of Three Pikes
{Author_32}Albrecht of Tisenbreck, from his book "The Art of Siege"
{Author_33}Elector Count Mikael Ludenhof, answering concerns over the state of his militia's equipment
{Author_34}Imperial Marksman Saying.
{Author_35}Grand Theogonist Volkmar
{Author_36}Daranis, Warrior Priest of Sigmar
{Author_37}Halgar Halfhand
{Author_38}Van Dire's Prohecy, Liber Chaotica
{Author_39}Mordrek, cursed Champion of Chaos
{Author_40}Tarok of the Khazag Tribe
{Author_41}Egrimm van Horstmann, former Grand Magister of the Order of Light
{Author_42}Egrimm van Horstmann, former Grand Magister of the Order of Light
{Author_43}Egrimm van Horstmann, former Grand Magister of the Order of Light
{Author_44}Insane scribblings written in the entrails of a still living man, after he had pulled them out with his bare hands.
{Author_45}Liber Chaotica, the Book of Khorne
{Author_46}Excerpt from "The Satin Verse", spoken by Slaanesh itself
{Author_47}Liber Chaotica, the Book of Slaanesh
{Author_48}Tal'Gatha the Fallen
{Author_49}Kargos Bloodspitter, Champion of Khorne
{Author_50}Kargos Bloodspitter, Champion of Khorne
{Author_51}Archaon, Lord of the End Times
{Author_52}Archaon, Lord of the End Times
{Author_53}Arbaal the Undefeated, at the Siege of Praag
{Author_54}Warcry of the Chosen of Khorne
{Author_55}Vlad von Carstein
{Author_56}Mannfred von Carstein
{Author_57}Count Haagen Vrahk the Cold
{Author_58}Teclis, High Loremaster of the Kingdom of Saphery, Twin to Tyrion the Defender, Last of Aenarion's Line
{Author_59}Dwarven Saying
{Author_60}Dwarven Saying
{Author_61}Dwarven Saying
{Author_62}Dwarven Saying
{Author_63}Berndt Lavaspear, from his book "The Dwarfish Art of War"
{Author_64}Durgrim Redman, Dwarf Hammerer
{Author_65}Gotrek Gurnisson, Trollslayer
{Author_66}Morglum Necksnapper
{Author_67}Grimgor Ironhide
{Author_68}Goff, Orc Stateejatist... Strajeejatist... Strateejarist... Ahh, Sod it... Boss
{Author_69}Rozgar, Veteran Squig Herder
{Author_70}Morglum Necksnapper
{Author_71}Chief Engineer Boris Kraus of Nuln
{Author_72}Albrecht of Nuln
{Author_73}Liber Malefic
{Author_74}Wurrzag Ud Ura Zahubu
{Author_75}Grand Theogonist Rueben Wrolfgar 
{Author_76}Alaric, High Theogonist of Sigmar
{Author_77}Volkmar, Grand Theogonist of Sigmar
{Author_78}Witch Hunter Captain Helmur van Hal
{Author_79}The Deus Sigmar - 3, 34:5
{Author_80}Bernhardt Hal, Witch Hunter General
{Author_81}Klaus Heldbrenkt, from his book "Memoirs of a Doctor"
{Author_82}Otto Kriess, Witch Hunter
{Author_83}Ulren the Tracker
{Author_84}Devin Weibruber, Roadwarden
{Author_85}Ulfred Wasmeier, Priest of Sigmar
{Author_86}Karl Althaus, Imperial Pikeman 
{Author_87}Sigmar Unberogen
{Author_88}Caterina Confalone, Priestess of Myrmidia
{Author_89}Teaching of the Priests of Sigmar
{Author_90}Reiklander Joke
{Author_91}Count Marius Leitdorf of Averland
{Author_92}Refugee, following the sack of Hergig
{Author_93}Graf Boris Todbringer of Middenland
{Author_94}Duke Leopold von Bildhofen
{Author_95}Stirlander Proverb
{Author_96}Sigmar Unberogen
{Author_97}Ludmilla von Thieldorf, Reikland Noble
{Author_98}Seiger Weisgerber, Chief Librarian of the Light Order
{Author_99}Colonel Senf von Scharf, on matters of camp discipline.
{Author_100}Roadwarden Saying
{Author_101}Last known words of Sheriff Prester Nordlingen
{Author_102}Common phrase of Tollkeepers across the Empire.
{Author_103}Hargin Hook-hand, Dwarven Innkeeper
{Author_104}Bederich the Bowman, Kislevite Kossar
{Author_105}Edgar Furfoot, Halfling Hunter
{Author_106}Herfl, Knight's Squire. And staying that way, most likely.
{Author_107}Shavandrel Half-sighted, One-eyed Master Waywatcher of the Asrai
{Author_108}Foster Braybrook, Halfling Vampire Hunter
{Author_109}Captain Diederick Nieman, Master and Commander of the "Ingrid"
{Author_110}Algernon Dussollier, Blood Dragon Vampire in the service of the Red Duke of Mousillon
{Author_111}Elise Nacht, Mutant
{Author_112}Kirsten Stumfnasse, Vampire Hunter
{Author_113}Excerpt from the Saga of Sigmar
{Author_114}Graf Boris Todbringer, Elector Count of Middenheim
{Author_115}Liber Chaotica, from the "Book of Khorne"
{Author_116}Unknown, describing Khorne, the God of Blood
{Author_117}Haubr, Norsemen
{Author_118}Alakreiz, Kurgan
{Author_119}Zar Sezask, Kurgan Chief
{Author_120}Deitzaad, Kurgan Shaman
{Author_121}Zar Uzelek, Yusak Chief
{Author_122}A worthless promise.
{Author_123}Azeekel, Kurgan
{Author_124}Children's Rhyme of Ostland
{Author_125}Excerpt from the heretical ravings of Baron Otto von Daubler
{Author_126}Hermann Hackgut, Chosen of Khorne
{Author_127}Excerpt from the "Saga of Khorne"
{Author_128}Beginning of the "Song of Death"
{Author_129}Excerpt from the "Song of Death"
{Author_130}Kardos Aqshyash Phaos'Y
{Author_131}Unidentified Beastman
{Author_132}Unidentified Orc
{Author_133}Unidentified Cat
{Author_134}Liliog, Doombull of Tzeentch
{Author_135}Dwarven Proverb
{Author_136}Dwarven Proverb
{Author_137}Dwarven Proverb
{Author_138}Dwarven Proverb
{Author_139}Dwarven Proverb
{Author_140}Elanlik Zakakragellason, Dwarf Giantslayer
{Author_141}Korbad Grimaxe, Dwarf Explorer
{Author_142}Dwarf Merchant
{Author_143}From the "Epic of Morgrim"
{Author_144}Dwarf King Alrik at the defence of Karak Hirn
{Author_145}Dwarf King Alrik at the defence of Karak Hirn
{Author_146}Dwarf King Alrik at the defence of Karak Hirn
{Author_147}Indronlil Shining Helm, Shadow Warrior
{Author_148}Lord Alasir, about the Druchii
{Author_149}Shazamel, Witch Elf
{Author_150}Teilancarr, Druchii Corsair
{Author_151}Dimitri, Kislevite Blacksmith
{Author_152}Constatin von Carstein
{Author_153}Sylvanian Proverb
{Author_154}Count von Sangster, Vampire
{Author_155}Countess Lucretia, Vampire
{Author_156}Lady Ariette von Carstein, Vampire
{Author_157}Countess Isabella, wife to Vlad von Carstein, Vampire
{Author_158}Sir Tiberius Kael, Blood Dragon Vampire
{Author_159}Konrad von Carstein, Vampire
{Author_160}Mannfred von Carstein, Vampire
{Author_161}Mannfred von Carstein, Vampire
{Author_162}Countess Isabella, wife to Vlad von Carstein, Vampire
{Author_163}Zacharias the Everlasting
{Author_164}Lady Ariette von Carstein, Vampire, on the virtues of Wights
{Author_165}Mannfred von Carstein, Vampire
{Author_166}Mannfred von Carstein, Vampire
{Author_167}Liber Necris
{Author_168}Liber Necris
{Author_169}Liber Necris
{Author_170}Grimoire Necronium, Chapter XII, from the "The Book of W'Soran"
{Author_171}Gnashrag, Orc Warboss
{Author_172}Gnashrag, Orc Warboss
{Author_173}Snigit, Gobbo Charioteer, sort of
{Author_174}Gazbag, Orc Warboss, to Snigit the Goblin Charioteer
{Author_175}Gazbag, Orc Warboss, on the qualities of a chariot driver
{Author_176}Gabber, Orc
{Author_177}Galnast, Orc Boss
{Author_178}Galnast, Orc Boss
{Author_179}Galnast, Orc Boss
{Author_180}Gitsniker, Goblin Boss
{Author_181}Sheglak, Orc Great Shaman
{Author_182}Figlak, Night Goblin
{Author_183}Snotlings
{Author_184}Liber Malefic
{Author_185}Marshal Neiber, to one of his aide-de-camps
{Author_186}Borodyn, Kislevite Winged Lancer Rotamaster
{Author_187}Skarkeetah, Slave Lord of the Kurgan
{Author_188}von Margur, Hero of Altdorf
{Author_189}Drogo Hance, Averland Greatsword
{Author_190}Skarkeetah, Slave Lord of the Kurgan
{Author_191}Zar Uldin, Kurgan Chief
{Author_192}Mengil Manhide, Captain of the "Manflayers" Regiment of Renown
{Author_193}Mengil Manhide, Captain of the "Manflayers" Regiment of Renown
{Author_194}Ruglud, Captain of the "Armoured Orcs" Regiment of Renown
{Author_195}Johann van Hal, Witch Hunter
{Author_196}Last words of Bernardo 'The Rat'
{Author_197}Leopold, Captain of the "Leopard's" Regiment of Renown
{Author_198}Overheard in the Ol' Pig an' Whistle Inn, Marienburg
{Author_199}Oglah Khan, Captain of the "Wolfboyz" Regiment of Renown
{Author_200}Adelrond of Couronne
{Author_201}Unknown, describing a charge of the Silver Helms
{Author_202}High Elven proverb
{Author_203}Tyriel, the Archmage of Saphery
{Author_204}Shadow Warriors' motto
{Author_205}Marius, Veteran Sellsword
{Author_206}Wissenlander Zealot Hunter
{Author_207}Gurni Thorgrimson, Troll Slayer, seeing a Juvenile Wyvern
{Author_208}Ostlander Farmer
{Author_209}Imperial Proverb
{Author_210}Liber Tzeentch
{Author_211}Liber Khorne
{Author_212}Liber Nurgle
{Author_213}Liber Slaanesh
{Author_214}Survivor of Praag about the Blue Horrors
{Author_215}Dark Zealot of Chaos
{Author_216}Bule, Lord of Pus
{Author_217}Suriel Lianllach, Imperial Scholar, describing Chaos Knights
{Author_218}Gurni Thorgrimson, Troll Slayer, just before fighting with a Bloodthirster
{Author_219}Gavius Klugge, Priest of Sigmar, on a Totem of Gork
{Author_220}Unknown Orc seconds before his death
{Author_221}An Orc shaman unleashing the Foot of Gork
{Author_222}Orc Saying
{Author_223}Ugrok Beardburna, Orc Warboss
{Author_224}Snotling Pump Wagon operator
{Author_225}Unknown Skaven Gutter Runner
{Author_226}Gurni Thorgrimson, Troll Slayer, fighting with Skaven Wind Globadiers
{Author_227}Greyseer Thanquol
{Author_228}Deathmaster Sniktch
{Author_229}Witch Hag's Curse
{Author_230}Witch Elves Saying
{Author_231}Dark Elf Shades motto
{Author_232}Imperial Scholar on Corsairs of Ghrond
{Author_233}Flagellant Battle Cry
{Author_234}Reiksguard Saying
{Author_235}Imperial Proverb
{Author_236}Dwarven Proverb
{Author_237}Dwarven Proverb
{Author_238}Dwarven Proverb
{Author_239}Dwarven Proverb
{Author_240}Johannes Broheim, Imperial Scholar
{Author_241}Ancient Hammerer saying
{Author_242}Gavius Klugge, Imperial Scholar, on Gurni Thorgrimson
{Author_243}Last words of an Imperial soldier attacked by Lizardmen Kroxigor
{Author_244}Countess Iseara
{Author_245}Grom the Paunch
{Author_246}Azhag the Slaughterer
{Author_247}Crooked Teff Goblin
{Author_248}Sntunty Smasha
{Author_249}Gavius Klugge discribing Big 'Uns
{Author_250}Snotling Sabouter
{Author_251}Orc Iron Boyz's battle cry
{Author_252}Savage Boyz's saying
{Author_253}Imperial soldier describing Morathi
{Author_254}Malekith
{Author_255}Sorceress of Ghrond
{Author_256}Druchii noble
{Author_257}Angi'arie - Druchii Witch
{Author_258}Disciple of Malekith
{Author_259}Veteran Quarreler
{Author_260}Thorgrim Grudgebearer
{Author_261}Long Drong's Pirate
{Author_262}Volkmar the Grim
{Author_263}Karl Franz
{Author_264}Bright Wizard Acolyte
{Author_265}Black Knight of Morr
{Author_266}Kairos Fatewever
{Author_267}Archaon
{Author_268}Teclis
{Author_269}Tyrion
{Author_270}Keeper of the Flame
{Author_271}Battle Pilgrims
{Author_272}Unknown Clan Rat
{Author_273}Sergent Feipel's last words
{Author_274}Bronn Greybeard
{Author_275}Classic goblin battleplan
{Author_276}Jacob Roedwig, Halberdier
{Author_277}Nemain Feagh, Witch Hag
{Author_278}Bronn Greybeard
{Author_279}Mountain Guard
{Author_280}Skaven clawleader Niktitt, explayning yet another failure
{Author_281}Jacob Roedwig, Halberdier on Inner Circle Knights
{Author_282}Inner Circle Preceptor
{Author_283}Bronn Greybeard
{Author_284}"Mad" Alexander Sturmisch, Celestial Wizard casting Chain Lighting spell
{Author_285}Squig Hopper
{Author_286}Orc saying
{Author_287}Jacob Roedwig, Halberdier about a Wyvern
{Quote_1}No matter which provinces you serve, no matter which tour of duty you pull, no matter what town you call home, the enemy is out there waiting.
{Quote_2}There are many paths by which the enemy attack, and sometimes these routes lie within each of us.
{Quote_3}Now, load and prime.
{Quote_4}Tell the Baron on no account to enter the hills to the south. Tell him to stay by Thunder River. I would not have it on my conciensce that he ventured into the Geistenmund Hills unwarned.
{Quote_5}A heroes death is for fools.
{Quote_6}"Brother", spoke the four as one, "together we shall rule, surrender to the darkness within your heart you know holds true."
{Quote_7}In his hand the Sword of Khaine did promise power untold as God of Light and God of Murder battled for his soul.
{Quote_8}One by one the daemons fell and elf lord he stood tall, for should he fail upon his task then mortal world would fall.
{Quote_9}Upon the Isle beneath the fight, wise mages cast their spells, and daemon minions howled in anguish, cursed to an eternal hell.
{Quote_10}And on this day we bow our heads to he who world did save, Aenarion the Proud Defender, Aenarion the Ever Brave.
{Quote_11}We are the people of Ulthuan, and as we suffer the pain of our past, so does she.
{Quote_12}Neither mortal nor god could withstand his wrath.
{Quote_13}There is nothing more for you to study in the ways of fighting. Now you must study your own heart.
{Quote_14}We ride until the sun sets, and only then do we cease... Of all our weapons, our steeds are our greatest.
{Quote_15}They are not just guardians of a temple, they are the chosen warriors of a mighty elven god.
{Quote_16}With the thunder of hooves and the turning of our steel shod wheels, we are death upon the wind. 
{Quote_17}With bow in hand, ours is a vengeance, rained down from afar, we are death upon the wind.
{Quote_18}With talls spears held to our foes throat, cold fury guiding our aim, we are death upon the wind.
{Quote_19}An army that seeks to fight without protection of the Eagles Claws is clearly courageous or inept. Either way, I wish no part in it.
{Quote_20}Yes they drink blood. Yes, some of them have been known to command armies of the damned. But at least they're not Elves.
{Quote_21}They are stronger than us, smarter than us, live longer than us, and far better looking than us. They are our superiors in every respect, and the taxes are lower when they rule. When they come back I will be the first to welcome them.
{Quote_22}We shall strike down our foes with sharp steel and cold hearts. The weak die so that the strong prevail and none shall be spared. Then only then will our enemies know the true meaning of fear.
{Quote_23}Athel Loren shall not suffer the presence of Man, nor Orcs, nor Dwarfs, nor Beastmen. If a foe takes a single step upon such sacred soil, they shall not take another.
{Quote_24}Three things make The Empire great – faith, steel and gunpowder!
{Quote_25}Fear is the shadow to the light of our bravest deeds.
{Quote_26}And thus I command Thy Soul to the eternal grace of Sigmar Divine. Few, if any, have done more for this illustrious Empire the Lord Sigmar entrusted to us, and it is indeed a united Realm that mourn Thy Depature. Fare well, Magnus, most pious of Servants.
{Quote_27}Take their word, take their women, take their horses, their goods, their food. Just leave their land and money.
{Quote_28}I think there's too many of them this time.
{Quote_29}These poor, simple folk - too fearful or too dull-witted to see the vulgarity and evil in their own midst. They wail and complain about my... uncompromising methods, but who among you can say that hanging half a village is too high a price to pay for the assurance that corruption has been exposed and destroyed this day?
{Quote_30}Be vigilant and strong. Who knows what evil lurks in the vacillation of a weak fool.
{Quote_31}Walls can't dodge!
{Quote_32}If the battlements are carried, throw all your strength there. Such an advantage is always dearly won.
{Quote_33}I don't expect them to fight, I expect them to die.
{Quote_34}It's like shooting goblins in a gorge.
{Quote_35}All Men dream, but not in the same way. Those, who dream at night, in the dark of their minds, awake in the morning to see that it was all an illusion. But those, who dream at day, are dangerous people. Their dreams are dreams of hope, dreams of betterment, dreams of change. Out of those come forth the accursed followers of chaos.
{Quote_36} Stand fast, Sons of Sigmar! Ours is the good fight, and we shall prevail! FOR SIGMAR AND THE EMPIRE!
{Quote_37}Never forgive, never forget.
{Quote_38}These are the End Times, when te jagged claw of Chaos tears out at the heart of the world and the Dark Gods feast upon the doom of mortals.
{Quote_39}I no longer have the right to pray to Sigmar, but by the demons who guard the gates to the realm of chaos, i pray for your salvation. Rest now, for all eternity. You have escaped the painful struggle of war.
{Quote_40}I have returned, father, to claim my birthright and my destiny. Once you spared me death, such was your folly. I shall not make the same mistake. By right of bith and conquest I claim leadership of the Khazag in the name of the true gods.
{Quote_41}Woe, O world! The Age of Mortals is coming to an end. Time passes into oblivion, and the stars lapse in the sky.
{Quote_42}The dreadful breed of night is crawling out of darkness, to take possession of the world. Fools! Seek refuge in faith or madness, for there's no longer any other place to hide. 
{Quote_43}The Reign of Chaos has begun.
{Quote_44}Nurgle's children, our sweetest, our favourites...how much Nurgle loves his children, how much Nurgle loves his little darlings...
{Quote_45}Your eyes are on me, your strength is with me, your armour covers me, your hatred fills me.
{Quote_46}Through the souls of your borthers and sisters I take My place amongst the Three; through their pleasure I ascend my Throne.
{Quote_47}Pleasure, for Pleasure's sake.
{Quote_48}Burn! Burn with the fires of Change! Scream your hymns to Tzeentch!
{Quote_49}I embrace death without regret as I embraced life without fear.
{Quote_50}I would rather die having glimpsed eternity than never to have stirred the cold furrow of mortal life. 
{Quote_51}Fear me mortals, for I am the Anointed, the Favoured Son of Chaos, the Scourge of the World.
{Quote_52}The armies of the gods rally behind me, and it is by my will and by my sword that your weakling nations shall fall.
{Quote_53}Fill the moat with the corpses of your comrades. Trample on their broken carcasses to reach the ramparts. Bring down the walls with the weight of the dead.
{Quote_54}Blood for the Blood God! Skulls for the Skull Throne!
{Quote_55}Surrender and serve me in life, or die and slave for me in death.
{Quote_56}We are the masters of night, and humans are but our cattle. While we walk upright, they're on their knees.
{Quote_57}Arise from your graves and obey my will! As you are, so were we. As we are, so shall ye.
{Quote_58}An Ancient blade shattered in the war of the beard, almost symbolic of that feud. Forged by the Dwarfs, enchanted by the Elves, broken by their conflict.
{Quote_59}There's nothin' as sure in the world as the glitter of gold and the treachery of Elves.
{Quote_60}Put your trust in stone and iron - stone and iron have always been true friends of the Dwarfs.
{Quote_61}Manling coins are like their words: never trust them. Use your weighing scales and keep your axe handy!
{Quote_62}Hi ho, hi ho, it's off to war we go...
{Quote_63}Arrows are useless against a castle - you can only win by using heavy wall-breaching equipment, which is why dwarfs are the superior race in siege warfare.
{Quote_64}There ain't nowt a cannon can do that a determined Dwarf with a hammer can't achieve.
{Quote_65}Not that I have anything against senseless violence, manling, but why exactly are you strangling that old man?
{Quote_66}The only good stunty is a dead stunty, and the only thing better than a dead stunty is a dyin' stunty who tells yer where to find 'is mates.
{Quote_67}I'm gonna stomp 'em to dust. I'm gonna grind their bones. I'm gonna pile 'em up inna big fire and roast 'em. I'm gonna bash 'eads, break faces and jump up and down on da bits dat are left. An' den I'm gonna get really mean.
{Quote_68}Orkses is never beaten in battle. If we win we win, if we die so it don't count as beat. If we runs for it we don't die neither, so we can always come back for anuvver go, see!
{Quote_69}I call dis one 'ere Gerty...she's not much to look at, but d'ose horns 'n teef 'll put even da oldest Ironbreakas 'n a panic.
{Quote_70}Let 'em tell da King. Da east belongs to da Orcs. Da east belongs to Morglum. Da east is green.
{Quote_71}There are no problems that cannot be solved with cannons.
{Quote_72}All life consists of highly organised matter, governed by the laws of nature. Thus all life is a struggle against Chaos, a struggle that is ultimately destined to be lost.
{Quote_73}They come to claim us for their dark masters, to choke the world in decadence, to drown it in disease and blood. What hope can there be for the mortal world? It is assailed by nightmares and its most dangerous dreams, each one given murderous form by the power of ancient and terrible gods.
{Quote_74}Im off to find Da Git, Anyone comin?
{Quote_75}It is not the strong enemy we must fear, the danger lies with the weak who flock to their banner.
{Quote_76}No man can be judged until he stands alone before his god.
{Quote_77}The daemons of Chaos can be likened to hungry and rabid wolves. The sheperd should not waste his time hating the wolf that attacks his flock. He should simply kill it.
{Quote_78}At some point in his life, every man finds himself confronted by the reality of evil. The test comes in whether he is willing to face it unflinching, or turn aside and by his inaction let that evil prosper.
{Quote_79}And then, calling his armies to Him, Sigmar did go to the Middle Mountains, He did find Himself confronted by a sinful horde, And making His Hammer He did cast the Ratmen down.
{Quote_80}Thus was gathered into Mordheim on the eve of its destruction all the sins of men together, as a boil gathers the poisons of the body ready to be lanced by the surgeon's knife.
{Quote_81}As a physician, I have witnessed many strange things in my career, but nothing prepared me for the man who had grown exceptionally long and a sharp tooth out from the top of his head...
{Quote_82}Unless the Emperor seals our borders, we are doomed. And even if he did at once, I fear it is far too late already.
{Quote_83}The nobles of our great Empire may claim to rule this land, but their reach stops at the shadow cast by the forests. For within, the Beastmen rule.
{Quote_84}Harden your hearts and let no pity soften them. They are the spawn of Chaos and it is our task, our duty to destroy them.
{Quote_85}No matter how many abominations we destroy, the Chaos Waste spits out more than before.
{Quote_86}It is better to take your own life than to fall into the hands of the Kurgan.
{Quote_87}Let us take strength from our diversity.
{Quote_88}Myrmidia said to find the enemy's weak spot and attack it with overwhelming force. This applies in war, politics, and yes, even love.
{Quote_89}What holds the Empire together, lad, is that our mutual dislike of each other is less than our dislike of everyone else.
{Quote_90}How does an Averlander tell a difference between his woman and his cattle? He can't!
{Quote_91}Sigmar Preserve us, but I often put much more trust in the Dwarfs than I do in my fellow Electors.
{Quote_92}Hochland was once the light of the East. Now, it's just embers.
{Quote_93}As long as the fire of the Great Temple lasts, Middenheim and Middenland will never fall.
{Quote_94}Middenheim is like a great leech, sucking the blood from honest Middelanders. Perhaps recent events hold the key to our freedom.
{Quote_95}Quick thinkin' makes for fast mistakes.
{Quote_96}I am Sigmar. I am Golden. I am God. Harken for my name, for it will echo redoubled through the ages. It will strike down my enemies wherever they may hide. It will be heard when the need is greatest.
{Quote_97}Father rests with Morr now. And we clubbed together enough to pay the Priests to make sure the bastard stays there.
{Quote_98}The horrors that reside within the Wastes of Chaos are mere reflections of the nightmares that exist just beyond its reach.
{Quote_99}I know it was you that killed him, you rotter. Now own up before I give you a bloody good thrashing.
{Quote_100}Watchmen have gaols. Roadwardens have bullets.
{Quote_101}Look, look, no, no, thank you, but I don't WANT your daughters virtue, Frau Banhoff. Although I'm sure It's very nice.
{Quote_102}Fivepenceplease... Watchudoinwitdatknife?..
{Quote_103}If yer know what's good for yer, leave right now. If yer don't, I'll rip yer from arsehole to breakfast.
{Quote_104}Haha! Anozzer byllzchei! See iff yoo can beat zat, komrad!
{Quote_105}You wouldn't last a minute in the wilds, city boy. I may be half your height, but I'm twice the man.
{Quote_106}Surry, sur, Oi wuz wutchin' a squirl, watchu sayin'?
{Quote_107}I don't both need my eyes to spot humans. I can smell the filthy beasts from a mile away.
{Quote_108}Don't be misled; the vampires screams are just an act. Only the living can feel pain. Unfortunately.
{Quote_109}You believe I insulted you? Well, sir, I congratulate you on on your perspicacity.
{Quote_110}Look into my eyes. They will be the last thing you will ever see.
{Quote_111}The human world does not want me. Here is where I belong.
{Quote_112}You can always tell Vampires by their eyes; they hold disdain and dreadful need in equal measure. But carry a mirror as well.
{Quote_113}Into the darkness, came a light. A torch of the gods, A dragon with two tails...
{Quote_114}Give me an enemy I may meet with strong steel and stout oak in my hands, not a dagger in the night and an accounting-book.
{Quote_115}From the blood sea rose eight mighty creatures each with the heads of dogs and the bodies of lions, and each one yoked with great chains of brass.
{Quote_116}He sits atop a throne of blood, From which a river flows, Its tributaries are pain and want, Its tributaries are pain and want,
{Quote_117}I pity you and all the world, that of all the races of Men, for the Gods favour we Norse alone.
{Quote_118}You may call us heathens, savages, even brutes, but we are the closest to the Gods. We see their work in all things. And we do not create new seemly Gods that conform with our hopes for the world.
{Quote_119}Why do we raid your lands? It is the will of the Gods.
{Quote_120}We are the prophets, we are the servants, we are the warriors of Tchar, and we will destroy you.
{Quote_121}There is nothing if there isn't war.
{Quote_122}Word of a Hung.
{Quote_123}Never trust a Hung. Destroy and eat them, yes. Never trust them.
{Quote_124}The Lord of Flies will eat your eyes, When your last breath gives out. And if you cry before you die, He'll kill you with the gout!
{Quote_125}Slaanesh is alive, and all that he asks is for us to love each other for who we are...
{Quote_126}Blood is for the Blood God. Not for drinking.
{Quote_127}My Lord is the Beginning and he is the End. He is Master of Mortals, and the core of our Dead Hearts.
{Quote_128}Despair all ye nations, deny not that we're sick. For our blood is like water where once it was thick. 
{Quote_129}And our minds have grown leaden, our bodies gone weak, And venom pours from our lips whenever we speak.
{Quote_130}War. There is only war.
{Quote_131}Grrrraaaaawwwwwrrrrrrr!
{Quote_132}Waaaaagh!
{Quote_133}Miaow!
{Quote_134}I hear it always. The sweet, sweet song of blood. Oftimes I must use Tchar's gifts to scorch the meat, which destroys some flavour. Always more, though. The feast never ends.
{Quote_135}The test of a shield is in the way it withstands battle. The test of an ale is in how it ages in the barrel. The rest of an arch in how long it stands up. The test of an individual is in how long he lives.
{Quote_136}To lack gold is to lack a pit-prop against the caven-ins of misfortune, to lack a shield against the arrows of spite.
{Quote_137}The blades of enemies may steal your old age. Thieves may steal your gold. Slander may steal your reputation. But skill, once learned, you keep forever.
{Quote_138}Tradition must be respected, for it is the voice of our ancestors.
{Quote_139}Gold cannot buy lost honour, nor craft repair it.
{Quote_140}Never trust an Elf, I always say. Dark, light, high, purple, doesn't matter. All the same to me.
{Quote_141}Are there Chaos Elves? No. There are only the Druchii, the Dark Elves, those renegade kin from Ulthuan. Though some prostrate themselves before the Serpent, by and large, their entire culture seems to exist to serve Khaine, the Lord of Blood and Murder. Sounds like Khorne? Well, maybe. But the Witch Elves look nothing like the Chaos Marauders.
{Quote_142}Averlands are not bad for manlings. They're solid in character, stick to their word, and don't put on airs like those nose-in-the-air Reiklanders. And they make the best manling beer in the south. Well, that's not saying much, but you won't choke on it!
{Quote_143}History shall not deride, That Morgrim fled his father's side!"
{Quote_144}We fight to protect our kinfolk, we fight to defend our clans, but more importantly we fight to uphold our honour.
{Quote_145}Ne'er forget the torment we have suffered and for each and every wrong our enemies heaped upon our ancestors, they shall repay the debt in blood.
{Quote_146}For we are sons of Grugni; alone we are rocks, united we stand with the strength of a mountain.
{Quote_147}They are soulless reavers, deluded by their own corruption. Can they not see the madness that lies within the Witch King? Their very nature is anathema to our rich culture and heritage. I mourn for them even as I slay them.
{Quote_148}Who are they? They are sorrow. Pain. Misery.
{Quote_149}The unwashed hordes of the Hung represent everything I hate about Humans. They stink, they're fools, and they are all too easily corrupted by Chaos.
{Quote_150}To sail with a Black Ark is one of the greatest honours that any Druchii could ever aspire to.
{Quote_151}The hordes of the Kurgan are more than the stars in the skies. They are savage, fight without honour, and want nothing more than to eradicate the Empire, root and branch.
{Quote_152}I do not care what our prey think of us. Do you consider what opinion meat has of you?
{Quote_153}The Dead walk fast.
{Quote_154}The apparent failures of immortals are, seen over the true course of time, the merest of setbacks.
{Quote_155}My kiss shall bring you eternity...and the greatest of power.
{Quote_156}And what in this world worth having does not come with a price of pain or suffering?
{Quote_157}Let there ever be wine, and blood, and slaughter! Restraint is for mortals.
{Quote_158}When the hunt is loosed, the hounds are held back so the fox may make ground and the chase have length in it. Such are our curses too, for the Gods seek to raise the most sport they can from our hunting.
{Quote_159}The sun and the silver cannot harm us--not if we will them not to. Not if we truly belive they will not.
{Quote_160}It seems to me that life is like a fast-flowing stream, and the mortals upon the world are like sticks and leaves caught helpless in its grip, dragged on through life, age, and into death.
{Quote_161}Thus we see all things come and go, empires rise and fall, all things once strong become weak. All things, of course, save ourselves.
{Quote_162}It's a game, yes, but there are rules. There are always rules, except for us.
{Quote_163}Today is a good day to be dead.
{Quote_164}Unquestioningly loyal. Infallibly brave. The pinnacle of the necromantic arts. If I had a hundred such as them, I could conquer any nation, rout any army -- and never lack for comraderie either. Although, they are typically poor conversationalists.
{Quote_165}I don't torture you because I enjoy it. I do it because I need you to understand what I am capable of, because I need you to be afraid.
{Quote_166}This land is my home, my birthright. The wind and rain are my allies. The trees and stones are my foot soldiers. The very earth will rise up against you should you try to take it from me. And my people will feast on your bones.
{Quote_167}Awake O Dead, for there can be no rest for ye beneath the earth. Let the splintered bones burrow from the grave pall.
{Quote_168}Let cold fingers grip time-worn blades, and unseeing eyes survey the fields of slaughter. For your time has come once more.
{Quote_169}And the dead shall walk.
{Quote_170}And they will rise from their graves to march upon the world of the living. Each and every mortal that falls will swell their numbers until only a world of darkness remains. Only then will the world know of the eternal order that lies within the peace of Undeath.
{Quote_171}Nar! Yer spoiling da plan!
{Quote_172}Gork save us... Wot a bunch of gitz.
{Quote_173}Sorry Boss!
{Quote_174}Dat's the third chariot you've wrecked dis week...
{Quote_175}'E loves goin' too fast an' dun care 'bout iz safety.
{Quote_176}Oi! Snebber! Woz you lookin' at my choppa? Wot? Howzabout you looks at it a bit closer eh? Yeah? Yeah? Eat dis!
{Quote_177}We iz strong an' tough. Da strong onez win, an' then eat the weak.
{Quote_178}Some of dem Gobboes is awright to keep for slaves or ter catch Humie cannonballs in the heads but most is best fer the pot.
{Quote_179}One day we eats all of youse. One day soon.
{Quote_180}Da humies look at yer, an see a big joke. Orcs, too. Let 'im laugh while yer tick'lin dere guts wit yer sticker. 'member always dat yer smaller, so's ya got's to be smarter, eh?
{Quote_181}Gork and Mork made da Goblinz for us to kick, kill, and eat. Dey iz nothing. Dey iz less than nothing. Even dere magic iz weak an' pointless. Only use Dey got in a fight iz catchin' Humie arrows. Wiv der 'eads.
{Quote_182}It's a sort of symbio--a symbeer--a connection 'tween us and da Squigs, dat means dey eat us sometimes and we eat dem, too. A bit like humies and us. Whaddya mean ya don't eat us when you catch us? Why not?
{Quote_183}Look! Humie! Fight it fight it fight it! Jab jab jab! Get it get it get it! Yarrrggg!
{Quote_184}Horrors are pink, horrors are blue, Where once there was one, now there are two!
{Quote_185}I ought to have you shot. Hah! Ha ha! Shot! Have Schott Shot! Ha ha ha!
{Quote_186}We are Yetchitch krug! We are the Riders of the Dead!
{Quote_187}You have no idea where you are or what you are about to become. Tchar will show you real radiance. Tchar will untwist your fibres and allow you to see. You are blessed, and you do not yet know it.
{Quote_188}I am a spurred and sworn knight of Karl Franz, may his majesty shine for ever, great is his radiance. You will have no hold over me, daemon.
{Quote_189}Damn you! We're dead! We're dead here! Give me back my blade so I can slit my own throat and have done! Spare me the pain they will inflict on us!"
{Quote_190}Blue. Like the sky. Blue, like the mutable truth of Tchar.
{Quote_191}Tchar rejoices in change, and the second holiest change in the world is the change from life to death.
{Quote_192}It's not about the money, friend. I do this because I enjoy it.
{Quote_193}Don't worry. Your skin will soon be joining that of your benefactor.
{Quote_194}Gobbos fer dinner! Gobbos fer tea! Gobbos when u want ’em! Gobbos for me!
{Quote_195}It's a witch!
{Quote_196}Miserable, do-gooding, no-account, back-stabbing, underhand... 's getting' so an honest landlord can't even relieve a bunch of farmers of their crops without someone stickin' their ugly noses in. Bunch of lousy, dog-breath... NO I HAVEN'T ANY LAST WORDS!..
{Quote_197}For the Leopard!
{Quote_198}No, no, they didn't look dangerous, more a bunch of rich kids out to show off their new armour. Very flashy they were, all gems and silk. We'll have a bit of fun we though. Easy pickings, we thought. Well anyone can make a mistake. Poor old Captain Malvino, last mistake he ever made.
{Quote_199}You payz, we slayz!
{Quote_200}And with one final blow, his blade driven by his faith in the Lady, Marcus of Bordelaux slew the fell lord of the Norse, ending the battle that had raged for night and day atop the towering lighthouse of L'Anguille..."
{Quote_201}A glittering wave of unstoppable knights...
{Quote_202}We do not so easily fall into temptation.
{Quote_203}I shall see the High Elves return to glory!
{Quote_204}We are as the night, so our brothers may embrace the sun.
{Quote_205}Only one side lives to spend their money...
{Quote_206}Do unto evil as evil hath done unto you.
{Quote_207}This monster is but a youngin. Not even worth the fight.
{Quote_208}The fields produce whatever has been planted. This year we grow corpses...
{Quote_209}Often in war, information is worth more than weapons.
{Quote_210}The only constant is change!
{Quote_211}Blood! Hate! Skulls! Rage!
{Quote_212}There is strength in the sickness. Give in to the plague.
{Quote_213}Who wouldn't want to be stronger, faster, more beautiful?
{Quote_214}Gibbering and capering, to gaze upon them is to gaze into change.
{Quote_215}Let me introduce you to...pain!
{Quote_216}And may the flesh forever rot from thy very bones in eternal infestation!
{Quote_217}The thick armour fused to their mutated bodies seems to swell and grow with time.
{Quote_218}A worthy death, as long as it goes with me.
{Quote_219}A foul offering to one of their degenerate gods.
{Quote_220}Uh oh, dat shaman's got too much WAAAGH! in 'im. He's gonna blow!
{Quote_221}Time fer all 'umies, stunties, squeakies, and weak 'uns ta say bye-bye!
{Quote_222}Da best part of bein' an orc is smaching fings!
{Quote_223}Da stunties is askin' for a beatin'?
{Quote_224}Fasta! Fasta! Fasta! Oh no! - Too Fast!
{Quote_225}Stab slice in the dark. Kill foolish man-things in their burrows.
{Quote_226}Cover your mounths, the air is death!
{Quote_227}Boneripper, quick quick. Bite slay kill!
{Quote_228}Slay kill. Poison does for man-things, point-ear, and dwarf-thing alike.
{Quote_229}You shall serve me consciously, and for all eternity!
{Quote_230}Let the blood flow like a river!
{Quote_231}At home in the darkness, at one with the night.
{Quote_232}The sea is cruel, but pales in comparison to these natural born killers.
{Quote_233}Our deaths are upon us. The End Times are here!
{Quote_234}A knight's training is never over. We improve...or we die.
{Quote_235}We shall not bend, we shall not falter, we shall not break.
{Quote_236}A dwarf device - deadly and reliable forever.
{Quote_237}A Dwarf's home is where his axe hangs.
{Quote_238}Grudges are best buried with the corpses of the wrongdoer.
{Quote_239}Each dwarf appears carved from the rock he makes his home.
{Quote_240}We could see a legion of fierce dwarfs silhouetted against the peaks.
{Quote_241}The hammer blow rings out doom to our foe.
{Quote_242}A proud dwarf, before he took his slayer oath.
{Quote_243}Aaaaaaagh!
{Quote_244}Look into my eyes. Listen to my voice. Bend to my will.
{Quote_245}Them elves ain't all that scary. Deyz just stunties who'z a bit taller.
{Quote_246}Wyvern's is good fer one thing, eatin' smashin' smellin' and flyin.' They're also good fer lettin' the other boyz know who's boss!
{Quote_247}If itz shiny itz mine!
{Quote_248}Da hills is alive wit da sound uv smashin'!
{Quote_249}Red eye brutes, the larger ones seem to be the natural leaders of their kind.
{Quote_250}Shinies is mine! I take da shinies from dis machine ere.
{Quote_251}Bash 'em! Crush 'em! Eat 'em!
{Quote_252}Orcz don' need metal an' stoopid toyz. Orcz don' need nuffink!
{Quote_253}I shivered at the sight of her - her beauty far beyond that of mortal man. But her soul glowed with an inner darkness that chilled my very core.
{Quote_254}If they shall not bow to me, the rightful ruler of Ulthuan, then I shall see each tower crumble and every soul scourged in pain, until they beg for my rule.
{Quote_255}The pathetic magic of men is nothing compared to the might of dark magic!
{Quote_256}Dispose of this slave, it seems to have broken.
{Quote_257}Your skin parts like silk.
{Quote_258}A scream in the night, a blade in the back, these are things of art.
{Quote_259}I swear I never saw a beard so white or gold as I saw on the features of Grombrindal.
{Quote_260}With Grungni's blood within my veins, and Valaya's wisdom on my brow I shall not rest until every grudge is exacted in vengeance.
{Quote_261}Yo ho, yo ho, a pirate's death for me!
{Quote_262}I have looked into the very heart of chaos and survived. If a humble servant of Sigmar such as myself can do so, then there is hope for all men.
{Quote_263}Will you not die for your Empire? Will you not fight for your families? Sally forth then, into the jaws of death and cry havoc this day, that you may live within the annals of history!
{Quote_264}Bring forth the enemy so I may heat them on the bonfire.
{Quote_265}May Morr guide you in the death I bring you.
{Quote_266}We see that which was and thus we know your secrets. We see that which shall be and thus we know your fate. The now is trivial to us - we know the day we perish is not this day.
{Quote_267}Fear me, mortals, for I am the Anointed, the Favoured Son of Chaos, the Scourge of the World. The armies of the gods rally behind me, and it is by my will and by my sword that your weakling nations shall fall.
{Quote_268}Lileath knows the purity of my intentions - I would see the shackles of Chaos broken.
{Quote_269}Our fate brings us here, and our fate sends us home! Forth! Forth now! For Ulthuan and the day of our destiny!
{Quote_270}While I live, the Flame of Asuryan shall burn.
{Quote_271}Blessed is the Grail Knight we follow.
{Quote_272}Quick, quick. You go first. I guard your tail.
{Quote_273}Steady, lads. This Doombull can't get past us if we hold the line!
{Quote_274}Not pigs, lad. Boars. Big difference.
{Quote_275}Keep 'ittin' 'em until dey stopz movin'. Den lootz!
{Quote_276}I hear they bathe in blood to stay young and beautiful forever. Don't always work, though.
{Quote_277}It takes the blood of three full-grown slaves to fill my couldron. Don't waste a drop!
{Quote_278}This? This is nothing, lad. That time in the peaks when I'd lost me quarrels, me firestone, and me ale? That was bad.
{Quote_279}...and when those gnobi followed my tracks up the slope, I collapsed, oh, about twenty thousand stone of ice and snow atop their heads. So we needm't worry about the Frozen Nose tribe no more.
{Quote_280}It's not my fault! Iskritt lead-went down the badwrong tunnel. There were beard-dwarfs there.
{Quote_281}They think they're so great, with their shiny armour and noble birth and majestic steeds and superior battle training and - okay, so they are pretty good.
{Quote_282}There's no foe that can't be beat with a strong arm, faith in Sigmar, and the well-timed charge of sixty men on horseback.
{Quote_283}By the blood of Grungni, they shall pay. By heart and hold, by wrath and ruin, by oath honour it is sworn!
{Quote_284}Eenie, meenie, minie - oh, why choose?
{Quote_285}Hang on tight, dis iz gonna be a bumpy ride...
{Quote_286}Da orc what fights an'runz away can alwayz come back f'r anudder go, see?
{Quote_287}The creature fell upon us like a thunderstorm, sudden and loud, all roaring and gnashing its teeth. Hans died immediately to the thing's claws. Erich to its jaws. The captain drove it off and we thought that was the last of things, but the captain didn't last long with its poison in him...
